[{"ID":"QFIA","users":[{"ID":"XELO","name":""},{"ID":"LGXC","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"XELO","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["LGXC"],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"question":{"ID":195,"question":"Mollit ut consequat non do nulla commodo sint ullamco in laborum?","answers":[{"answer":"nostru","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"pariat","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"in fugiat","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem veniam","points":42,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"question":{"ID":119,"question":"Quis adipisicing eiusmod proident officia proident nisi nulla deserunt duis veniam commodo?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"in","points":69,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"question":{"ID":275,"question":"Consequat cillum est nisi nulla et pariatur voluptate pariatur ex incididunt?","answers":[{"answer":"sint","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi tempor","points":45,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse sunt","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":53,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"question":{"ID":261,"question":"Velit cupidatat commodo pariatur proident pariatur esse labore ad exercitation commodo excepteur?","answers":[{"answer":"commod eu","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt labore","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"do","points":56,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607189690291,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"MKKC","users":[{"ID":"LXZS","name":""},{"ID":"IIYZ","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"LXZS","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["IIYZ"],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":true,"currentStage":2,"question":{"ID":104,"question":"Cillum aute incididunt occaecat ullamco et esse?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit do","points":60,"answered":true},{"answer":"ad mollit","points":73,"answered":true},{"answer":"eiusmo ad","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt","points":46,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"question":{"ID":193,"question":"Sit adipisicing tempor est?","answers":[{"answer":"nisi","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"commod","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"nostru esse","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":67,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"question":{"ID":6,"question":"Eiusmod adipisicing ea amet adipisicing eiusmod deserunt irure?","answers":[{"answer":"fugiat","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor nulla","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":85,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"question":{"ID":288,"question":"Velit proident ex fugiat excepteur esse adipisicing id sunt ea?","answers":[{"answer":"occaec id","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis Lorem","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt ex","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam esse","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida aliqui","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori","points":40,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607194510017,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"WGDF","users":[{"ID":"LZGB","name":""},{"ID":"NYWB","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"RXCS","name":""},{"ID":"ZRIP","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"LZGB","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["NYWB","ZRIP"],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"question":{"ID":141,"question":"Reprehenderit sunt ad aute officia voluptate?","answers":[{"answer":"irure pariat","points":46,"answered":true},{"answer":"veniam","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"elit","points":45,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo enim","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru ea","points":56,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"question":{"ID":170,"question":"Aliquip occaecat eiusmod tempor enim est tempor labore cupidatat?","answers":[{"answer":"volupt nulla","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse offici","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut consec","points":77,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"question":{"ID":190,"question":"Consectetur commodo fugiat officia labore voluptate?","answers":[{"answer":"enim repreh","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit et","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi minim","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu dolore","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"except laboru","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa consec","points":66,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"question":{"ID":261,"question":"Velit cupidatat commodo pariatur proident pariatur esse labore ad exercitation commodo excepteur?","answers":[{"answer":"commod eu","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt labore","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"do","points":56,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607196900822,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"QJWU","users":[{"ID":"LZGB","name":""},{"ID":"NYWB","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"RXCS","name":""},{"ID":"ZRIP","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"RXCS","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["NYWB","ZRIP"],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":true,"currentStage":1,"question":{"ID":230,"question":"Culpa elit aliqua laboris nulla ex deserunt nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"ut","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat","points":44,"answered":true},{"answer":"mollit","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"qui","points":55,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"question":{"ID":91,"question":"Do consectetur laborum nulla qui?","answers":[{"answer":"cillum","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc enim","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis laboru","points":61,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"question":{"ID":185,"question":"Velit dolor ipsum consequat laboris quis ex ex?","answers":[{"answer":"eiusmo ipsum","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt labore","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit","points":42,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"question":{"ID":197,"question":"Ipsum aute laboris adipisicing occaecat duis et Lorem duis?","answers":[{"answer":"duis nostru","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse anim","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"anim","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida conseq","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo","points":74,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607197275117,"activeTeam":1,"started":false},{"ID":"RODW","users":[{"ID":"WPJD","name":""},{"ID":"ILLN","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"WPJD","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["ILLN"],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":true,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":268,"question":"Aute mollit ea consequat velit ea proident et ex aute dolore sit?","answers":[{"answer":"amet","points":38,"answered":true},{"answer":"commod nulla","points":45,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"anim cupida","points":51,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":4,"question":"Ea esse ullamco incididunt magna sint qui?","answers":[{"answer":"id","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"labore ullamc","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":51,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":103,"question":"Commodo est irure nostrud labore cillum veniam?","answers":[{"answer":"sunt","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici Lorem","points":49,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":105,"question":"In tempor ullamco id ut ullamco cillum enim voluptate tempor ad?","answers":[{"answer":"irure","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"labore magna","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor offici","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"qui","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem","points":80,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607199031940,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"ONVM","users":[{"ID":"DHWP","name":""},{"ID":"AXTP","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"DHWP","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["AXTP"],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":246,"question":"Reprehenderit nostrud eu proident amet reprehenderit laboris consequat amet?","answers":[{"answer":"deseru","points":56,"answered":true},{"answer":"eiusmo","points":46,"answered":true},{"answer":"amet in","points":33,"answered":true},{"answer":"labori","points":32,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":245,"question":"Et enim incididunt minim proident eu sunt sint magna qui?","answers":[{"answer":"ullamc volupt","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit ipsum","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"do","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu in","points":41,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":284,"question":"Lorem magna exercitation consequat?","answers":[{"answer":"laboru eu","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"et est","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh eiusmo","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt culpa","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna id","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":78,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":25,"question":"Occaecat proident laboris eiusmod?","answers":[{"answer":"nostru","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"elit nulla","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"proide","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec laboru","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec incidi","points":81,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607205475336,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"UTRL","users":[{"ID":"PROX","name":""},{"ID":"LWRH","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"PROX","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["LWRH"],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":true,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":232,"question":"Et ipsum ipsum dolor?","answers":[{"answer":"incidi volupt","points":40,"answered":true},{"answer":"qui aute","points":58,"answered":true},{"answer":"laboru","points":61,"answered":true},{"answer":"exerci occaec","points":80,"answered":true},{"answer":"eu","points":84,"answered":true},{"answer":"ad cupida","points":48,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":210,"question":"Sunt sint consequat tempor cillum culpa?","answers":[{"answer":"quis non","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida aliqui","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor in","points":56,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":248,"question":"Irure mollit voluptate voluptate aute ipsum sint quis sint pariatur esse?","answers":[{"answer":"duis","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure consec","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq aliqui","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"labore adipis","points":75,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":178,"question":"Proident quis non duis?","answers":[{"answer":"cillum id","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"laboru labori","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"pariat","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo occaec","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim nulla","points":59,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607208463829,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"WRIU","users":[{"ID":"SHBI","name":""},{"ID":"GRBC","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"SHBI","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["GRBC"],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":true,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":6,"question":{"ID":235,"question":"Velit sit in laboris Lorem sunt nisi exercitation esse?","answers":[{"answer":"repreh","points":52,"answered":true},{"answer":"dolor","points":57,"answered":true},{"answer":"velit","points":53,"answered":true},{"answer":"ad","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici","points":71,"answered":true},{"answer":"nisi incidi","points":66,"answered":true},{"answer":"dolore labori","points":55,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":248,"question":"Irure mollit voluptate voluptate aute ipsum sint quis sint pariatur esse?","answers":[{"answer":"duis","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure consec","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq aliqui","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"labore adipis","points":75,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":291,"question":"Eu amet in occaecat elit minim et sint ipsum duis aliquip pariatur?","answers":[{"answer":"sunt","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat sint","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"elit","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim dolor","points":56,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":262,"question":"Adipisicing non nulla ipsum?","answers":[{"answer":"labori","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat","points":55,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607211932113,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"UTMT","users":[{"ID":"OFCH","name":""},{"ID":"CJHH","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"OFCH","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["CJHH"],"score":null},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":79,"question":"Laboris elit occaecat fugiat aliquip mollit do laborum reprehenderit aute dolore?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit aliqua","points":54,"answered":true},{"answer":"deseru quis","points":56,"answered":true},{"answer":"et","points":62,"answered":true},{"answer":"amet aliqua","points":55,"answered":true},{"answer":"mollit","points":66,"answered":true},{"answer":"duis","points":76,"answered":true},{"answer":"conseq culpa","points":48,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":145,"question":"Anim incididunt consequat culpa culpa?","answers":[{"answer":"occaec","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor","points":58,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":75,"question":"Magna consequat ut non commodo ullamco?","answers":[{"answer":"incidi","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh commod","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"pariat ut","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad nostru","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem Lorem","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"laboru","points":84,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":36,"question":"Pariatur ad consequat adipisicing ipsum?","answers":[{"answer":"dolore nisi","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua ea","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse","points":79,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":2,"modified":1607212027767,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"ZJCI","users":[{"ID":"QEEM","name":""},{"ID":"RDRD","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"QEEM","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["RDRD"],"score":null},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":91,"question":"Do consectetur laborum nulla qui?","answers":[{"answer":"cillum","points":67,"answered":true},{"answer":"ullamc enim","points":48,"answered":true},{"answer":"repreh","points":38,"answered":true},{"answer":"adipis laboru","points":61,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":90,"question":"Nulla laboris mollit quis ea ullamco esse sint pariatur?","answers":[{"answer":"conseq nisi","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci commod","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse repreh","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc consec","points":54,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":31,"question":"Adipisicing reprehenderit ipsum nostrud esse?","answers":[{"answer":"ex","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat et","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo fugiat","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem volupt","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"nostru","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui","points":67,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":2,"question":"Officia sit pariatur labore sint occaecat excepteur occaecat ad do reprehenderit?","answers":[{"answer":"magna","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit esse","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"except occaec","points":83,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":2,"modified":1607212245645,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"FNHG","users":[{"ID":"CYRP","name":""},{"ID":"ALBD","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"LWXT","name":""},{"ID":"DSFW","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"PDCD","name":""},{"ID":"XNKQ","name":""}],"hostID":"CYRP","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["ALBD","DSFW"],"score":604},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":10,"question":"Do id non pariatur duis duis labore eiusmod enim Lorem pariatur fugiat?","answers":[{"answer":"ullamc","points":33,"answered":true},{"answer":"et dolore","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor nulla","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis labori","points":35,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":192,"question":"Velit aliquip laborum id officia laboris sunt mollit est pariatur enim amet?","answers":[{"answer":"ipsum cupida","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse nulla","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu anim","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"laboru nisi","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint","points":64,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":30,"question":"Minim est in officia velit dolore laborum ad excepteur?","answers":[{"answer":"pariat","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"in proide","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla labori","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat labore","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint tempor","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"nostru","points":32,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":117,"question":"Nisi culpa veniam dolore duis deserunt?","answers":[{"answer":"commod","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor occaec","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"aute ea","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim esse","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam nostru","points":62,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607212274311,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"UYYM","users":[{"ID":"CYRP","name":""},{"ID":"ALBD","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"LWXT","name":""},{"ID":"DSFW","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"PDCD","name":""},{"ID":"XNKQ","name":""}],"hostID":"LWXT","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["ALBD","DSFW"],"score":604},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":236,"question":"Voluptate ut duis officia?","answers":[{"answer":"et","points":81,"answered":true},{"answer":"quis deseru","points":36,"answered":true},{"answer":"et commod","points":77,"answered":true},{"answer":"culpa elit","points":68,"answered":true},{"answer":"consec","points":44,"answered":true},{"answer":"enim esse","points":34,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":11,"question":"Consectetur irure exercitation voluptate?","answers":[{"answer":"amet adipis","points":71,"answered":true},{"answer":"offici","points":43,"answered":true},{"answer":"offici minim","points":47,"answered":true},{"answer":"ullamc","points":32,"answered":true},{"answer":"aliqui","points":71,"answered":true}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":111,"question":"Irure enim laboris duis culpa amet cillum incididunt consectetur?","answers":[{"answer":"except","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"proide offici","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure deseru","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"commod","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"anim","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":44,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":110,"question":"Esse consequat culpa cillum aute cupidatat in et esse?","answers":[{"answer":"fugiat incidi","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"id sit","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":43,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":3,"modified":1607212323969,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"RRTX","users":[{"ID":"CYRP","name":""},{"ID":"ALBD","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"LWXT","name":""},{"ID":"DSFW","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"PDCD","name":""},{"ID":"XNKQ","name":""}],"hostID":"PDCD","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["ALBD","DSFW"],"score":604},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607212484256,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"JIXN","users":[{"ID":"CYRP","name":""},{"ID":"ALBD","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"LWXT","name":""},{"ID":"DSFW","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"PDCD","name":""},{"ID":"XNKQ","name":""}],"hostID":"XNKQ","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["ALBD","DSFW"],"score":604},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":73,"question":"Sit minim consectetur irure aliqua?","answers":[{"answer":"qui","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem ipsum","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem volupt","points":38,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":298,"question":"Commodo cillum non est?","answers":[{"answer":"nulla cillum","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"in amet","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"ipsum commod","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"pariat cillum","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem cillum","points":74,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":13,"question":"Adipisicing aliqua velit mollit excepteur velit?","answers":[{"answer":"nostru","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea duis","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla sunt","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi deseru","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"do","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt sint","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex velit","points":57,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":84,"question":"Cillum dolore occaecat id commodo commodo reprehenderit adipisicing?","answers":[{"answer":"conseq deseru","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"non irure","points":37,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607213967715,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"XVYO","users":[{"ID":"KJFH","name":""}],"hostID":"KJFH","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":247,"question":"Laboris incididunt amet amet exercitation tempor fugiat ad sint reprehenderit cupidatat id?","answers":[{"answer":"est ad","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru sit","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi","points":85,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":189,"question":"Elit cillum quis sit qui sunt consectetur id?","answers":[{"answer":"dolor","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse velit","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq in","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec adipis","points":84,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":159,"question":"Voluptate aliquip sunt et adipisicing nostrud voluptate officia deserunt voluptate?","answers":[{"answer":"quis proide","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui ex","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"do do","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"in","points":71,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":221,"question":"Laborum laborum adipisicing ex ut irure?","answers":[{"answer":"in","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici incidi","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc culpa","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori dolor","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa labore","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"proide","points":72,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607214200595,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"YVCP","users":[{"ID":"GSEZ","name":""}],"hostID":"GSEZ","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":513},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":227,"question":"Irure culpa enim amet eu ea voluptate ullamco?","answers":[{"answer":"labore velit","points":59,"answered":true},{"answer":"volupt","points":36,"answered":true},{"answer":"anim ea","points":35,"answered":true},{"answer":"veniam aute","points":35,"answered":true},{"answer":"magna aliqua","points":33,"answered":true},{"answer":"ut cillum","points":78,"answered":true},{"answer":"dolore","points":45,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":290,"question":"Sint nulla elit dolor laborum esse dolor?","answers":[{"answer":"aliqui","points":47,"answered":true},{"answer":"ex duis","points":49,"answered":true},{"answer":"veniam","points":47,"answered":true},{"answer":"velit","points":49,"answered":true}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":12,"question":"Dolore minim dolor cupidatat do dolor nisi ipsum ut ea?","answers":[{"answer":"est anim","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"ipsum","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt pariat","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi","points":45,"answered":false},{"answer":"anim","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"in","points":76,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":296,"question":"Commodo minim eiusmod esse dolore?","answers":[{"answer":"ex","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim volupt","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"et elit","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":65,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":3,"modified":1607214586685,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"IUUI","users":[{"ID":"VWVW","name":""},{"ID":"YRDJ","name":"Teej"},{"ID":"YPDS","name":"Raymond"},{"ID":"CXED","name":"Teej 2"}],"hostID":"VWVW","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["YRDJ","CXED"],"score":1886},{"name":"Team 2","players":["YPDS"],"score":280}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":298,"question":"Commodo cillum non est?","answers":[{"answer":"nulla cillum","points":42,"answered":true},{"answer":"in amet","points":61,"answered":true},{"answer":"ipsum commod","points":51,"answered":true},{"answer":"pariat cillum","points":52,"answered":true},{"answer":"Lorem cillum","points":74,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":184,"question":"Eu culpa quis ex eu elit occaecat nostrud nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"tempor ut","points":53,"answered":true},{"answer":"deseru non","points":63,"answered":true},{"answer":"volupt enim","points":77,"answered":true},{"answer":"tempor nulla","points":64,"answered":true},{"answer":"eiusmo sunt","points":64,"answered":true},{"answer":"exerci amet","points":34,"answered":true}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":4,"question":{"ID":90,"question":"Nulla laboris mollit quis ea ullamco esse sint pariatur?","answers":[{"answer":"conseq nisi","points":44,"answered":true},{"answer":"exerci commod","points":34,"answered":true},{"answer":"ea","points":44,"answered":true},{"answer":"esse repreh","points":80,"answered":true},{"answer":"ullamc consec","points":54,"answered":true}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":true,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":32,"question":"Adipisicing exercitation ea do culpa ad laboris quis adipisicing ea?","answers":[{"answer":"quis","points":52,"answered":true},{"answer":"pariat","points":42,"answered":true},{"answer":"ex nisi","points":78,"answered":true},{"answer":"nisi sunt","points":32,"answered":true},{"answer":"fugiat","points":51,"answered":true}]}}],"currentRound":4,"modified":1607834451075,"activeTeam":0,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"ELBR","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"QVWB","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607280547568,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"IKXD","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"EMWG","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607281018349,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"VJBR","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"PVHX","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607281064028,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"XITZ","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"TSTR","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607281067385,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"GPXO","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"GYNO","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607281161994,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"UBQW","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"KVPY","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607281161998,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"IRXV","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"UVBB","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607281178887,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"ZQZP","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"ORQM","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607281283745,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"YIXN","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"QVJH","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607284348532,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"CTPM","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"WSHW","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607284414236,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"FFBE","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"OBGN","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607284537435,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"FQBY","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"HMMT","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607285188249,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"LIZK","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"TGHQ","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607285294625,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"DPDX","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"PTHV","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607285390018,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"MDQB","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"ADBQ","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607285522110,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"FGLZ","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"TKTJ","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607285619626,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"EMBS","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"JBID","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607285661454,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"LUVB","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"IURQ","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607285700851,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"PCBC","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"THXX","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607285731657,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"OLKX","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"PQAW","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607285756651,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"MWBB","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"VEIT","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607285775143,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"GEKG","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"QPOY","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607286020604,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"SQBA","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"XMCA","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607286034093,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"XVKI","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"INCM","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607287007499,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"HBEY","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"KSML","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607287153104,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"HKZM","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"KMCC","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607287295090,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"MUCI","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"SPKP","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607287343927,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"TVYQ","users":[{"ID":"QVWB","name":""},{"ID":"EMWG","name":""},{"ID":"PVHX","name":""},{"ID":"TSTR","name":""},{"ID":"GYNO","name":""},{"ID":"KVPY","name":""},{"ID":"UVBB","name":""},{"ID":"ORQM","name":""},{"ID":"QVJH","name":""},{"ID":"WSHW","name":""},{"ID":"OBGN","name":""},{"ID":"HMMT","name":""},{"ID":"TGHQ","name":""},{"ID":"PTHV","name":""},{"ID":"ADBQ","name":""},{"ID":"TKTJ","name":""},{"ID":"JBID","name":""},{"ID":"IURQ","name":""},{"ID":"THXX","name":""},{"ID":"PQAW","name":""},{"ID":"VEIT","name":""},{"ID":"QPOY","name":""},{"ID":"XMCA","name":""},{"ID":"INCM","name":""},{"ID":"KSML","name":""},{"ID":"KMCC","name":""},{"ID":"SPKP","name":""},{"ID":"PZPT","name":""}],"hostID":"PZPT","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607288552689,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"QHYU","users":[{"ID":"BWEJ","name":""},{"ID":"XCUG","name":""},{"ID":"HONO","name":""},{"ID":"FTQW","name":""},{"ID":"MCKI","name":""},{"ID":"VWOE","name":""},{"ID":"JTUO","name":""},{"ID":"DHUD","name":""}],"hostID":"BWEJ","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607290429926,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"DIFC","users":[{"ID":"BWEJ","name":""},{"ID":"XCUG","name":""},{"ID":"HONO","name":""},{"ID":"FTQW","name":""},{"ID":"MCKI","name":""},{"ID":"VWOE","name":""},{"ID":"JTUO","name":""},{"ID":"DHUD","name":""}],"hostID":"XCUG","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607290457081,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"CFOG","users":[{"ID":"BWEJ","name":""},{"ID":"XCUG","name":""},{"ID":"HONO","name":""},{"ID":"FTQW","name":""},{"ID":"MCKI","name":""},{"ID":"VWOE","name":""},{"ID":"JTUO","name":""},{"ID":"DHUD","name":""}],"hostID":"HONO","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607290494146,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"DXEV","users":[{"ID":"BWEJ","name":""},{"ID":"XCUG","name":""},{"ID":"HONO","name":""},{"ID":"FTQW","name":""},{"ID":"MCKI","name":""},{"ID":"VWOE","name":""},{"ID":"JTUO","name":""},{"ID":"DHUD","name":""}],"hostID":"FTQW","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607290558959,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"CUJF","users":[{"ID":"BWEJ","name":""},{"ID":"XCUG","name":""},{"ID":"HONO","name":""},{"ID":"FTQW","name":""},{"ID":"MCKI","name":""},{"ID":"VWOE","name":""},{"ID":"JTUO","name":""},{"ID":"DHUD","name":""}],"hostID":"MCKI","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607290570630,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"LBLW","users":[{"ID":"BWEJ","name":""},{"ID":"XCUG","name":""},{"ID":"HONO","name":""},{"ID":"FTQW","name":""},{"ID":"MCKI","name":""},{"ID":"VWOE","name":""},{"ID":"JTUO","name":""},{"ID":"DHUD","name":""}],"hostID":"VWOE","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607291032072,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"NJXG","users":[{"ID":"BWEJ","name":""},{"ID":"XCUG","name":""},{"ID":"HONO","name":""},{"ID":"FTQW","name":""},{"ID":"MCKI","name":""},{"ID":"VWOE","name":""},{"ID":"JTUO","name":""},{"ID":"DHUD","name":""}],"hostID":"JTUO","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607291638507,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"LLWX","users":[{"ID":"BWEJ","name":""},{"ID":"XCUG","name":""},{"ID":"HONO","name":""},{"ID":"FTQW","name":""},{"ID":"MCKI","name":""},{"ID":"VWOE","name":""},{"ID":"JTUO","name":""},{"ID":"DHUD","name":""}],"hostID":"DHUD","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607291961923,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"HGDQ","users":[{"ID":"LHBX","name":""}],"hostID":"LHBX","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607292073037,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"JTEC","users":[{"ID":"ERHY","name":""},{"ID":"VKTG","name":""},{"ID":"OGDO","name":""}],"hostID":"ERHY","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":270,"question":"Cupidatat nostrud proident Lorem nostrud Lorem proident consectetur consequat exercitation?","answers":[{"answer":"laboru","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem cupida","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore amet","points":74,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":131,"question":"Et Lorem exercitation elit veniam?","answers":[{"answer":"esse dolor","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis non","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem cupida","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"et anim","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida eiusmo","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor incidi","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna non","points":40,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":249,"question":"In in officia ad cillum duis sunt veniam officia dolor aliquip?","answers":[{"answer":"aliqua laboru","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"do","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"est","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore aliqua","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"elit nulla","points":32,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":284,"question":"Lorem magna exercitation consequat?","answers":[{"answer":"laboru eu","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"et est","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh eiusmo","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt culpa","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna id","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":78,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607293366014,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"DTKQ","users":[{"ID":"ERHY","name":""},{"ID":"VKTG","name":""},{"ID":"OGDO","name":""}],"hostID":"VKTG","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":258,"question":"Commodo aliquip nisi consequat?","answers":[{"answer":"consec","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor elit","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"duis","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec","points":51,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":100,"question":"Eiusmod non ex exercitation aliqua nulla?","answers":[{"answer":"dolore","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"except adipis","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim offici","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi nostru","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori","points":58,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":274,"question":"Sunt ex ullamco fugiat irure dolore in deserunt aliqua?","answers":[{"answer":"dolore","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici irure","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"do quis","points":80,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":253,"question":"Irure commodo deserunt eu do qui dolore pariatur occaecat aliquip?","answers":[{"answer":"dolor ea","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore magna","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"pariat","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici veniam","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat quis","points":34,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607293395757,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"OMQT","users":[{"ID":"ERHY","name":""},{"ID":"VKTG","name":""},{"ID":"OGDO","name":""}],"hostID":"OGDO","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":227,"question":"Irure culpa enim amet eu ea voluptate ullamco?","answers":[{"answer":"labore velit","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"anim ea","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam aute","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna aliqua","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut cillum","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":45,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":237,"question":"Ipsum consectetur elit veniam minim labore officia?","answers":[{"answer":"irure","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea ullamc","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet offici","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem minim","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"pariat labore","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi","points":56,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":244,"question":"Sunt cupidatat sunt magna pariatur sint dolore nisi amet laborum laborum eu?","answers":[{"answer":"cillum","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim anim","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis non","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit aliqua","points":62,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":29,"question":"Exercitation ipsum dolore fugiat?","answers":[{"answer":"enim","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex ea","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"qui","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"aute","points":36,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607293509779,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"UWKC","users":[{"ID":"OQEG","name":""},{"ID":"RDXL","name":""}],"hostID":"OQEG","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":193,"question":"Sit adipisicing tempor est?","answers":[{"answer":"nisi","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"commod","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"nostru esse","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":67,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":46,"question":"Sit et velit occaecat sint ea commodo incididunt dolore?","answers":[{"answer":"minim ut","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"commod offici","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse","points":40,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":229,"question":"Dolor nisi in Lorem est Lorem do ut?","answers":[{"answer":"minim dolore","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa ut","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"non qui","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut aute","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet aliqui","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam sint","points":53,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":3,"question":"Do occaecat consequat adipisicing Lorem aliqua exercitation minim nostrud fugiat non amet?","answers":[{"answer":"esse","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"et aliqui","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor ipsum","points":72,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607293537389,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"DGNX","users":[{"ID":"OQEG","name":""},{"ID":"RDXL","name":""}],"hostID":"RDXL","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":138,"question":"Mollit nisi in consequat quis elit exercitation deserunt?","answers":[{"answer":"conseq adipis","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore aliqua","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec","points":58,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":169,"question":"Velit exercitation eiusmod dolore magna?","answers":[{"answer":"consec aute","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"pariat cupida","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi labore","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa except","points":72,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":95,"question":"Velit nisi ex est ad nostrud?","answers":[{"answer":"volupt aliqui","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit nostru","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"elit sit","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea","points":41,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":167,"question":"Non aute incididunt anim qui in ea eu cupidatat consequat proident?","answers":[{"answer":"nisi","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"in","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru","points":45,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq amet","points":42,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607295982617,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"GYBS","users":[{"ID":"ZCRE","name":""},{"ID":"VOQG","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"ZCRE","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":162,"question":"Exercitation dolore enim est cupidatat proident occaecat elit id mollit excepteur?","answers":[{"answer":"ad","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut","points":82,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":57,"question":"Commodo ex qui incididunt nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"conseq fugiat","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc anim","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse tempor","points":52,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":8,"question":"Laborum qui do enim nisi incididunt aute fugiat id ut?","answers":[{"answer":"magna ad","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"est","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi proide","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure proide","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse ea","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"except","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"non deseru","points":66,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":46,"question":"Sit et velit occaecat sint ea commodo incididunt dolore?","answers":[{"answer":"minim ut","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"commod offici","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse","points":40,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607296639119,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"PKTP","users":[{"ID":"MRLD","name":""},{"ID":"SBPK","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"GDUE","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"KFNB","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"SBEX","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"OGTK","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"WJNP","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"UJBD","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"MRLD","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":207,"question":"Incididunt et et ut ut dolore anim sint et ullamco?","answers":[{"answer":"offici","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo incidi","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"do","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit eu","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea","points":38,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":177,"question":"Elit incididunt qui incididunt consequat consequat amet magna dolore?","answers":[{"answer":"deseru","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor labori","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse conseq","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit commod","points":65,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":45,"question":"Elit ex amet velit cillum?","answers":[{"answer":"sit sit","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim quis","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"aute sit","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc aliqua","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci ea","points":47,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":145,"question":"Anim incididunt consequat culpa culpa?","answers":[{"answer":"occaec","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor","points":58,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607300952886,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"QEDU","users":[{"ID":"EFYE","name":""},{"ID":"MLXS","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"ESWY","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"EFYE","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["ESWY"],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":99,"question":"Amet exercitation non enim fugiat deserunt eiusmod veniam qui sunt est?","answers":[{"answer":"ad","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"except qui","points":80,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":182,"question":"Sunt officia cupidatat proident do deserunt consectetur aute id voluptate duis nulla?","answers":[{"answer":"nostru sunt","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua velit","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad","points":47,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":3,"question":"Do occaecat consequat adipisicing Lorem aliqua exercitation minim nostrud fugiat non amet?","answers":[{"answer":"esse","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"et aliqui","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor ipsum","points":72,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":207,"question":"Incididunt et et ut ut dolore anim sint et ullamco?","answers":[{"answer":"offici","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo incidi","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"do","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit eu","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea","points":38,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607303339529,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"HPWY","users":[{"ID":"WFKB","name":""},{"ID":"WZYQ","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"AEJE","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"WFKB","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["WZYQ"],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":["AEJE"],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":true,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":127,"question":"Sint sint mollit nostrud ullamco amet incididunt tempor nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"labore","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"nostru labore","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi proide","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum occaec","points":48,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":103,"question":"Commodo est irure nostrud labore cillum veniam?","answers":[{"answer":"sunt","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici Lorem","points":49,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":15,"question":"Ullamco ad proident cillum commodo?","answers":[{"answer":"ut","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi non","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"elit","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet labore","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"non est","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"qui exerci","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt","points":71,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":14,"question":"Id esse ex aute minim aliquip ad mollit est?","answers":[{"answer":"Lorem et","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"nostru","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt","points":65,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607376646581,"activeTeam":1,"started":false},{"ID":"SOEI","users":[{"ID":"AEQN","name":""},{"ID":"OJFX","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"RKBG","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"AEQN","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["OJFX"],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":["RKBG"],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":true,"currentStage":1,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":160,"question":"Officia minim nulla culpa Lorem dolore irure anim anim adipisicing esse?","answers":[{"answer":"repreh qui","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"except mollit","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit fugiat","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori sit","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":54,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":238,"question":"Aute veniam mollit sunt elit Lorem velit anim voluptate?","answers":[{"answer":"velit ipsum","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"do deseru","points":46,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":17,"question":"Elit id commodo incididunt pariatur sint ad velit ipsum ad ad?","answers":[{"answer":"ullamc","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq eu","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat","points":45,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex","points":74,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":175,"question":"Aliquip mollit tempor sunt esse pariatur irure?","answers":[{"answer":"fugiat quis","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint commod","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq aliqua","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore eu","points":41,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607469117065,"activeTeam":1,"started":false},{"ID":"TXIP","users":[{"ID":"QUXJ","name":""},{"ID":"GXDL","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"MIQC","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"QUXJ","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["GXDL","MIQC"],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":true,"currentStage":3,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":104,"question":"Cillum aute incididunt occaecat ullamco et esse?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit do","points":60,"answered":true},{"answer":"ad mollit","points":73,"answered":true},{"answer":"eiusmo ad","points":67,"answered":true},{"answer":"sunt","points":46,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":270,"question":"Cupidatat nostrud proident Lorem nostrud Lorem proident consectetur consequat exercitation?","answers":[{"answer":"laboru","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem cupida","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore amet","points":74,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":119,"question":"Quis adipisicing eiusmod proident officia proident nisi nulla deserunt duis veniam commodo?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"in","points":69,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":252,"question":"Magna fugiat anim ipsum anim sunt sint?","answers":[{"answer":"dolor ullamc","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint esse","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc","points":33,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607559342632,"activeTeam":1,"started":false},{"ID":"GKQM","users":[{"ID":"ESMC","name":""},{"ID":"ZMIK","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"FKJQ","name":""},{"ID":"NUHR","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"ESMC","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["ZMIK","NUHR"],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":true,"currentStage":3,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":140,"question":"Quis ad non magna?","answers":[{"answer":"elit aliqui","points":54,"answered":true},{"answer":"qui","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"est in","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit nisi","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec sit","points":47,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":70,"question":"Laborum sunt et laboris labore?","answers":[{"answer":"cillum","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"proide","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori enim","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt aliqua","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi nisi","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"pariat","points":80,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":110,"question":"Esse consequat culpa cillum aute cupidatat in et esse?","answers":[{"answer":"fugiat incidi","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"id sit","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":43,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":60,"question":"Deserunt fugiat eiusmod aliquip occaecat reprehenderit in?","answers":[{"answer":"eu","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"qui","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna nisi","points":70,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607559373794,"activeTeam":1,"started":false},{"ID":"NIKX","users":[{"ID":"ESMC","name":""},{"ID":"ZMIK","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"FKJQ","name":""},{"ID":"NUHR","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"FKJQ","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["ZMIK","NUHR"],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":true,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":220,"question":"Enim consectetur culpa veniam consequat nisi aliqua?","answers":[{"answer":"culpa","points":33,"answered":true},{"answer":"velit aute","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi tempor","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec except","points":80,"answered":true},{"answer":"quis except","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida","points":77,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":95,"question":"Velit nisi ex est ad nostrud?","answers":[{"answer":"volupt aliqui","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit nostru","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"elit sit","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea","points":41,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":255,"question":"Aliquip magna tempor occaecat duis id nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"dolor","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"et est","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet ad","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad","points":64,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":199,"question":"Ipsum aute deserunt amet excepteur mollit?","answers":[{"answer":"magna ex","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam nostru","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"non","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis ullamc","points":39,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607559658411,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"FUIX","users":[{"ID":"MJMQ","name":""},{"ID":"QVTI","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"MJMQ","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["QVTI"],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":true,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":241,"question":"Ipsum fugiat nisi irure irure est qui voluptate ad occaecat reprehenderit?","answers":[{"answer":"elit dolore","points":33,"answered":true},{"answer":"occaec","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"except Lorem","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo elit","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex cupida","points":77,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":283,"question":"In excepteur aliquip culpa proident ex elit nostrud in?","answers":[{"answer":"dolor ex","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi qui","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"aute","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":34,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":287,"question":"Cillum officia incididunt mollit id non dolore anim in cupidatat?","answers":[{"answer":"dolor","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"est conseq","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor dolor","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":43,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":298,"question":"Commodo cillum non est?","answers":[{"answer":"nulla cillum","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"in amet","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"ipsum commod","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"pariat cillum","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem cillum","points":74,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607559900552,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"VJFW","users":[{"ID":"GESK","name":""},{"ID":"YEGO","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"GESK","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["YEGO"],"score":0,"points":null},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":true,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":272,"question":"Est id do consectetur aliquip nostrud officia laborum quis deserunt?","answers":[{"answer":"in minim","points":76,"answered":true},{"answer":"eiusmo","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt nisi","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"except","points":77,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":196,"question":"Adipisicing ullamco proident adipisicing ullamco ad deserunt nulla?","answers":[{"answer":"ullamc","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint sunt","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit id","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":49,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":117,"question":"Nisi culpa veniam dolore duis deserunt?","answers":[{"answer":"commod","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor occaec","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"aute ea","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim esse","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam nostru","points":62,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":179,"question":"In ullamco adipisicing deserunt dolor deserunt nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"Lorem pariat","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"laboru in","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"et nisi","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"aute commod","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":44,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607559930511,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"RINH","users":[{"ID":"VNNB","name":""},{"ID":"FKTQ","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"VNNB","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["FKTQ"],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":true,"currentStage":3,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":109,"question":"In sint sint sunt qui cupidatat elit laborum sint?","answers":[{"answer":"incidi quis","points":51,"answered":true},{"answer":"labori","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"et nisi","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt culpa","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"non","points":72,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":204,"question":"Duis voluptate elit quis in ullamco irure occaecat ex id?","answers":[{"answer":"volupt","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec nulla","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc tempor","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"proide labori","points":63,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":37,"question":"Adipisicing pariatur mollit eu reprehenderit consectetur enim esse minim?","answers":[{"answer":"irure","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"aute","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit","points":45,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":44,"question":"Ex irure deserunt ad ullamco enim ut anim aliqua ex?","answers":[{"answer":"proide adipis","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"ipsum occaec","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet velit","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"commod offici","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":74,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607560055017,"activeTeam":1,"started":false},{"ID":"DRWI","users":[{"ID":"FYQV","name":""},{"ID":"PHIA","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"VXXN","name":""},{"ID":"PGDV","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"CPFY","name":""},{"ID":"KOZA","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"QUBS","name":""}],"hostID":"FYQV","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["PHIA","PGDV","KOZA"],"score":194},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":true,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":88,"question":"Aliquip in reprehenderit sint reprehenderit ad reprehenderit sit occaecat laboris tempor mollit?","answers":[{"answer":"do","points":51,"answered":true},{"answer":"non conseq","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"non","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor labori","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna aliqui","points":82,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":10,"question":"Do id non pariatur duis duis labore eiusmod enim Lorem pariatur fugiat?","answers":[{"answer":"ullamc","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"et dolore","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor nulla","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis labori","points":35,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":255,"question":"Aliquip magna tempor occaecat duis id nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"dolor","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"et est","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet ad","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad","points":64,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":125,"question":"Ad voluptate amet deserunt aliquip amet dolor cillum voluptate laboris ut tempor?","answers":[{"answer":"anim irure","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci id","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"laboru elit","points":45,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607560327120,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"ZMSK","users":[{"ID":"FYQV","name":""},{"ID":"PHIA","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"VXXN","name":""},{"ID":"PGDV","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"CPFY","name":""},{"ID":"KOZA","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"QUBS","name":""}],"hostID":"VXXN","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["PHIA","PGDV","KOZA"],"score":194},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":true,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":168,"question":"Irure consequat veniam ad eiusmod deserunt nostrud id?","answers":[{"answer":"amet et","points":58,"answered":true},{"answer":"exerci quis","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"est","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"elit","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"id amet","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet ipsum","points":80,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":50,"question":"Esse pariatur non elit est non esse?","answers":[{"answer":"fugiat aliqui","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi eiusmo","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt Lorem","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec labore","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit culpa","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec","points":56,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":149,"question":"Consequat mollit velit ea quis culpa adipisicing eiusmod magna do irure irure?","answers":[{"answer":"id elit","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor except","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"id aliqua","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida","points":81,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":54,"question":"Quis proident pariatur voluptate ipsum magna eu et fugiat esse labore?","answers":[{"answer":"quis elit","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor est","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"aute","points":46,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607560492145,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"SEQV","users":[{"ID":"FYQV","name":""},{"ID":"PHIA","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"VXXN","name":""},{"ID":"PGDV","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"CPFY","name":""},{"ID":"KOZA","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"QUBS","name":""}],"hostID":"CPFY","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["PHIA","PGDV","KOZA"],"score":194},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":252,"question":"Magna fugiat anim ipsum anim sunt sint?","answers":[{"answer":"dolor ullamc","points":85,"answered":true},{"answer":"sint esse","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc","points":33,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":223,"question":"Eu eiusmod officia est id in?","answers":[{"answer":"conseq","points":45,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici irure","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq","points":60,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":85,"question":"Non irure consequat anim ut velit sint cupidatat?","answers":[{"answer":"Lorem","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim enim","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"non","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex sint","points":68,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":233,"question":"Ullamco et duis laborum mollit amet aute labore Lorem?","answers":[{"answer":"eiusmo","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa nulla","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam nostru","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"pariat","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua laboru","points":54,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607560540080,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"KWEK","users":[{"ID":"FYQV","name":""},{"ID":"PHIA","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"VXXN","name":""},{"ID":"PGDV","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"CPFY","name":""},{"ID":"KOZA","name":"player 1"},{"ID":"QUBS","name":""}],"hostID":"QUBS","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["PHIA","PGDV","KOZA"],"score":194},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":193,"question":"Sit adipisicing tempor est?","answers":[{"answer":"nisi","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"commod","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"nostru esse","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":67,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":166,"question":"Commodo ipsum elit enim?","answers":[{"answer":"quis","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"nostru","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"duis conseq","points":84,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":192,"question":"Velit aliquip laborum id officia laboris sunt mollit est pariatur enim amet?","answers":[{"answer":"ipsum cupida","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse nulla","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu anim","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"laboru nisi","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint","points":64,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":248,"question":"Irure mollit voluptate voluptate aute ipsum sint quis sint pariatur esse?","answers":[{"answer":"duis","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure consec","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq aliqui","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"labore adipis","points":75,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607560637602,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"KJCJ","users":[{"ID":"CSNH","name":""},{"ID":"VXYG","name":""}],"hostID":"CSNH","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":84},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":188,"question":"Ut aute est non cupidatat duis eu?","answers":[{"answer":"fugiat","points":84,"answered":true},{"answer":"tempor","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici qui","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis dolore","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis sit","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc","points":82,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":285,"question":"Ad anim fugiat adipisicing duis aliquip ad?","answers":[{"answer":"except","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"commod repreh","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"elit","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat exerci","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis mollit","points":39,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":202,"question":"Nisi est commodo ut culpa adipisicing enim consequat aliqua tempor quis et?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit elit","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit fugiat","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori ut","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc aute","points":66,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":128,"question":"Labore elit nostrud sunt nulla ad eu?","answers":[{"answer":"non","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi tempor","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"pariat ut","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim cupida","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet cillum","points":45,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607560667239,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"CNWM","users":[{"ID":"CSNH","name":""},{"ID":"VXYG","name":""}],"hostID":"VXYG","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":84},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":31,"question":"Adipisicing reprehenderit ipsum nostrud esse?","answers":[{"answer":"ex","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat et","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo fugiat","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem volupt","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"nostru","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui","points":67,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":125,"question":"Ad voluptate amet deserunt aliquip amet dolor cillum voluptate laboris ut tempor?","answers":[{"answer":"anim irure","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci id","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"laboru elit","points":45,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":93,"question":"Id officia id ea?","answers":[{"answer":"aute proide","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim quis","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis nulla","points":76,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":230,"question":"Culpa elit aliqua laboris nulla ex deserunt nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"ut","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"qui","points":55,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607560892696,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"JJXA","users":[{"ID":"QHQP","name":""},{"ID":"OHQD","name":""}],"hostID":"QHQP","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":363},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":284,"question":"Lorem magna exercitation consequat?","answers":[{"answer":"laboru eu","points":56,"answered":true},{"answer":"et est","points":33,"answered":true},{"answer":"repreh eiusmo","points":41,"answered":true},{"answer":"volupt culpa","points":69,"answered":true},{"answer":"magna id","points":36,"answered":true},{"answer":"dolore","points":50,"answered":true},{"answer":"magna","points":78,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":33,"question":"Incididunt sit ut non?","answers":[{"answer":"est ea","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat culpa","points":45,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa amet","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"labore eu","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"laboru exerci","points":43,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":131,"question":"Et Lorem exercitation elit veniam?","answers":[{"answer":"esse dolor","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis non","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem cupida","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"et anim","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida eiusmo","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor incidi","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna non","points":40,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":154,"question":"Velit minim ad esse esse in mollit tempor?","answers":[{"answer":"adipis culpa","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"except consec","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint repreh","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori et","points":66,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607560910496,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"HBSM","users":[{"ID":"QHQP","name":""},{"ID":"OHQD","name":""}],"hostID":"OHQD","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":363},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":179,"question":"In ullamco adipisicing deserunt dolor deserunt nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"Lorem pariat","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"laboru in","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"et nisi","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"aute commod","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":44,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":59,"question":"Pariatur labore officia do elit nulla consectetur cillum quis dolor ut ea?","answers":[{"answer":"pariat consec","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua qui","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse ut","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui ea","points":57,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":5,"question":"Adipisicing dolor culpa dolor laboris aliqua aliquip voluptate magna ipsum?","answers":[{"answer":"conseq sit","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea elit","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"labore","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim cillum","points":67,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":42,"question":"Duis esse amet quis id?","answers":[{"answer":"cillum","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"commod duis","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa","points":63,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607560931405,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"RXCC","users":[{"ID":"RNRU","name":""},{"ID":"SJIR","name":""}],"hostID":"RNRU","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":316},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":64,"question":"Qui exercitation ad consectetur irure aliqua?","answers":[{"answer":"pariat veniam","points":72,"answered":true},{"answer":"magna","points":80,"answered":true},{"answer":"nisi et","points":33,"answered":true},{"answer":"nulla","points":54,"answered":true},{"answer":"non","points":77,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":157,"question":"Exercitation consequat velit anim ipsum?","answers":[{"answer":"amet labori","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"proide minim","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"est","points":58,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":146,"question":"Et sunt incididunt consectetur elit?","answers":[{"answer":"labore","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"proide offici","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"qui elit","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc magna","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":78,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":199,"question":"Ipsum aute deserunt amet excepteur mollit?","answers":[{"answer":"magna ex","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam nostru","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"non","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis ullamc","points":39,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607560941562,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"CCIU","users":[{"ID":"RNRU","name":""},{"ID":"SJIR","name":""}],"hostID":"SJIR","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":316},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":83,"question":"Irure deserunt incididunt in adipisicing eu id velit?","answers":[{"answer":"cupida","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"aute","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"et repreh","points":63,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":128,"question":"Labore elit nostrud sunt nulla ad eu?","answers":[{"answer":"non","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi tempor","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"pariat ut","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim cupida","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet cillum","points":45,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":215,"question":"Esse id id amet aliquip consectetur excepteur officia non ullamco ipsum pariatur?","answers":[{"answer":"minim in","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"duis eiusmo","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"except nulla","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis dolor","points":82,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":227,"question":"Irure culpa enim amet eu ea voluptate ullamco?","answers":[{"answer":"labore velit","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"anim ea","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam aute","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna aliqua","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut cillum","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":45,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607560963986,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"KCED","users":[{"ID":"XZHA","name":""},{"ID":"BYIP","name":""}],"hostID":"XZHA","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":255},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":293,"question":"Minim est sunt et irure?","answers":[{"answer":"dolore mollit","points":71,"answered":true},{"answer":"exerci","points":46,"answered":true},{"answer":"incidi magna","points":62,"answered":true},{"answer":"esse","points":76,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":177,"question":"Elit incididunt qui incididunt consequat consequat amet magna dolore?","answers":[{"answer":"deseru","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor labori","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse conseq","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit commod","points":65,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":72,"question":"Tempor commodo aliqua dolore officia irure sunt quis exercitation sunt velit?","answers":[{"answer":"duis in","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"non","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"commod aute","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"duis irure","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua do","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"ipsum","points":65,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":249,"question":"In in officia ad cillum duis sunt veniam officia dolor aliquip?","answers":[{"answer":"aliqua laboru","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"do","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"est","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore aliqua","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"elit nulla","points":32,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607560972481,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"UXDX","users":[{"ID":"XZHA","name":""},{"ID":"BYIP","name":""}],"hostID":"BYIP","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":255},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":163,"question":"Laboris consectetur tempor in et duis Lorem amet deserunt enim?","answers":[{"answer":"ea sunt","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"do","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad duis","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit veniam","points":32,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":8,"question":"Laborum qui do enim nisi incididunt aute fugiat id ut?","answers":[{"answer":"magna ad","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"est","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi proide","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure proide","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse ea","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"except","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"non deseru","points":66,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":185,"question":"Velit dolor ipsum consequat laboris quis ex ex?","answers":[{"answer":"eiusmo ipsum","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt labore","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit","points":42,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":271,"question":"Laborum culpa velit incididunt eiusmod?","answers":[{"answer":"cupida","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"non dolore","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"ipsum","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"duis labori","points":51,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607561098582,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"YOMS","users":[{"ID":"CLBT","name":""},{"ID":"WNCC","name":""}],"hostID":"CLBT","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":274},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":93,"question":"Id officia id ea?","answers":[{"answer":"aute proide","points":80,"answered":true},{"answer":"repreh","points":50,"answered":true},{"answer":"minim quis","points":68,"answered":true},{"answer":"quis nulla","points":76,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":211,"question":"Qui eu dolore ex ad duis proident laboris id culpa incididunt est?","answers":[{"answer":"ad","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt laboru","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"labore ea","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet duis","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui nisi","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna nostru","points":51,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":105,"question":"In tempor ullamco id ut ullamco cillum enim voluptate tempor ad?","answers":[{"answer":"irure","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"labore magna","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor offici","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"qui","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem","points":80,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":67,"question":"Aliqua culpa enim non anim in adipisicing dolore quis enim?","answers":[{"answer":"nisi incidi","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc sit","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida aliqui","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"duis","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"nostru","points":45,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla","points":46,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607561107616,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"PABT","users":[{"ID":"CLBT","name":""},{"ID":"WNCC","name":""}],"hostID":"WNCC","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":274},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":176,"question":"Labore ullamco veniam eu ut deserunt adipisicing laborum?","answers":[{"answer":"et","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"laboru","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"except","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"ipsum","points":74,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":179,"question":"In ullamco adipisicing deserunt dolor deserunt nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"Lorem pariat","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"laboru in","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"et nisi","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"aute commod","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":44,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":30,"question":"Minim est in officia velit dolore laborum ad excepteur?","answers":[{"answer":"pariat","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"in proide","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla labori","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat labore","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint tempor","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"nostru","points":32,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":1,"question":"Dolore tempor sit aute cupidatat enim nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"quis sit","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat conseq","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt commod","points":43,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607561186569,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"GHEQ","users":[{"ID":"MPBW","name":""},{"ID":"JJEA","name":""},{"ID":"UMAB","name":""}],"hostID":"UMAB","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":277},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":247,"question":"Laboris incididunt amet amet exercitation tempor fugiat ad sint reprehenderit cupidatat id?","answers":[{"answer":"est ad","points":74,"answered":true},{"answer":"deseru sit","points":61,"answered":true},{"answer":"et","points":57,"answered":true},{"answer":"nisi","points":85,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":200,"question":"Amet fugiat aliqua fugiat eiusmod nulla voluptate eiusmod?","answers":[{"answer":"elit labori","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida deseru","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori deseru","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"in ut","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse dolor","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"est","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui","points":61,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":210,"question":"Sunt sint consequat tempor cillum culpa?","answers":[{"answer":"quis non","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida aliqui","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor in","points":56,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":115,"question":"Incididunt anim sit consectetur exercitation minim anim dolor?","answers":[{"answer":"id","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"anim","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"et mollit","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc nostru","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida enim","points":79,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607561407927,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"GHEQ","users":[{"ID":"MPBW","name":""},{"ID":"JJEA","name":""},{"ID":"UMAB","name":""}],"hostID":"UMAB","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":277},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":247,"question":"Laboris incididunt amet amet exercitation tempor fugiat ad sint reprehenderit cupidatat id?","answers":[{"answer":"est ad","points":74,"answered":true},{"answer":"deseru sit","points":61,"answered":true},{"answer":"et","points":57,"answered":true},{"answer":"nisi","points":85,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":200,"question":"Amet fugiat aliqua fugiat eiusmod nulla voluptate eiusmod?","answers":[{"answer":"elit labori","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida deseru","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori deseru","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"in ut","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse dolor","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"est","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui","points":61,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":210,"question":"Sunt sint consequat tempor cillum culpa?","answers":[{"answer":"quis non","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida aliqui","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor in","points":56,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":115,"question":"Incididunt anim sit consectetur exercitation minim anim dolor?","answers":[{"answer":"id","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"anim","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"et mollit","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc nostru","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida enim","points":79,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607561214000,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"GHEQ","users":[{"ID":"MPBW","name":""},{"ID":"JJEA","name":""},{"ID":"UMAB","name":""}],"hostID":"UMAB","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":277},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":247,"question":"Laboris incididunt amet amet exercitation tempor fugiat ad sint reprehenderit cupidatat id?","answers":[{"answer":"est ad","points":74,"answered":true},{"answer":"deseru sit","points":61,"answered":true},{"answer":"et","points":57,"answered":true},{"answer":"nisi","points":85,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":200,"question":"Amet fugiat aliqua fugiat eiusmod nulla voluptate eiusmod?","answers":[{"answer":"elit labori","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida deseru","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori deseru","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"in ut","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse dolor","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"est","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui","points":61,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":210,"question":"Sunt sint consequat tempor cillum culpa?","answers":[{"answer":"quis non","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida aliqui","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor in","points":56,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":115,"question":"Incididunt anim sit consectetur exercitation minim anim dolor?","answers":[{"answer":"id","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"anim","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"et mollit","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc nostru","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida enim","points":79,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607561214000,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"DONH","users":[{"ID":"DIZU","name":""},{"ID":"UGMB","name":""}],"hostID":"DIZU","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":346},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":43,"question":"Esse enim voluptate tempor?","answers":[{"answer":"ea","points":85,"answered":true},{"answer":"adipis","points":80,"answered":true},{"answer":"nostru","points":85,"answered":true},{"answer":"est","points":60,"answered":true},{"answer":"tempor sint","points":36,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":154,"question":"Velit minim ad esse esse in mollit tempor?","answers":[{"answer":"adipis culpa","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"except consec","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint repreh","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori et","points":66,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":114,"question":"Elit eu dolore consequat in sint voluptate culpa?","answers":[{"answer":"laboru","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"proide conseq","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla ea","points":62,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":182,"question":"Sunt officia cupidatat proident do deserunt consectetur aute id voluptate duis nulla?","answers":[{"answer":"nostru sunt","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua velit","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad","points":47,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607561418093,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"CJQI","users":[{"ID":"DIZU","name":""},{"ID":"UGMB","name":""}],"hostID":"UGMB","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":346},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":127,"question":"Sint sint mollit nostrud ullamco amet incididunt tempor nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"labore","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"nostru labore","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi proide","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum occaec","points":48,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":228,"question":"Aliquip non Lorem nisi cillum aute occaecat voluptate nulla?","answers":[{"answer":"ad aute","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici","points":65,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":81,"question":"Aute ullamco do amet eu?","answers":[{"answer":"offici","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"non","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa enim","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui","points":67,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":6,"question":"Eiusmod adipisicing ea amet adipisicing eiusmod deserunt irure?","answers":[{"answer":"fugiat","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor nulla","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":85,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607561425920,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"OHYE","users":[{"ID":"VJIF","name":""}],"hostID":"VJIF","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":100,"question":"Eiusmod non ex exercitation aliqua nulla?","answers":[{"answer":"dolore","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"except adipis","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim offici","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi nostru","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori","points":58,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":164,"question":"Duis minim proident minim deserunt do?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit sit","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum occaec","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"pariat","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut nulla","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum ex","points":60,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":60,"question":"Deserunt fugiat eiusmod aliquip occaecat reprehenderit in?","answers":[{"answer":"eu","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"qui","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna nisi","points":70,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":144,"question":"Adipisicing sunt mollit sint ipsum labore quis nulla?","answers":[{"answer":"culpa Lorem","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla laboru","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad aute","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor sit","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit mollit","points":46,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607561556591,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"ESQC","users":[{"ID":"KLPK","name":""}],"hostID":"KLPK","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":434},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":51,"question":"Deserunt laborum ipsum Lorem qui et reprehenderit?","answers":[{"answer":"et","points":49,"answered":true},{"answer":"eu","points":52,"answered":true},{"answer":"exerci","points":48,"answered":true},{"answer":"non","points":81,"answered":true},{"answer":"dolore ad","points":73,"answered":true},{"answer":"nulla fugiat","points":49,"answered":true},{"answer":"anim labore","points":82,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":272,"question":"Est id do consectetur aliquip nostrud officia laborum quis deserunt?","answers":[{"answer":"in minim","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt nisi","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"except","points":77,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":173,"question":"Duis consectetur sint nulla esse ipsum ad nostrud ea ullamco?","answers":[{"answer":"nulla enim","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla","points":33,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":98,"question":"Id exercitation nostrud aliqua exercitation pariatur?","answers":[{"answer":"ex","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu eu","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore labore","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec sint","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"laboru","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"in","points":85,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607561580313,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"UXQA","users":[{"ID":"LRBY","name":""}],"hostID":"LRBY","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":286},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":197,"question":"Ipsum aute laboris adipisicing occaecat duis et Lorem duis?","answers":[{"answer":"duis nostru","points":67,"answered":true},{"answer":"esse anim","points":33,"answered":true},{"answer":"anim","points":80,"answered":true},{"answer":"cupida conseq","points":32,"answered":true},{"answer":"eiusmo","points":74,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":104,"question":"Cillum aute incididunt occaecat ullamco et esse?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit do","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad mollit","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo ad","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt","points":46,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":276,"question":"Nulla eu Lorem occaecat commodo cupidatat?","answers":[{"answer":"amet","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex velit","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis","points":39,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":42,"question":"Duis esse amet quis id?","answers":[{"answer":"cillum","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"commod duis","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa","points":63,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607561600635,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"JSRH","users":[{"ID":"ZRXG","name":""}],"hostID":"ZRXG","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":422},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":198,"question":"Irure officia dolore fugiat officia?","answers":[{"answer":"aliqua","points":85,"answered":true},{"answer":"labore id","points":39,"answered":true},{"answer":"qui","points":68,"answered":true},{"answer":"deseru nulla","points":48,"answered":true},{"answer":"id deseru","points":63,"answered":true},{"answer":"aliqua elit","points":49,"answered":true},{"answer":"ad culpa","points":70,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":130,"question":"Enim laborum dolor id cupidatat mollit nisi ex officia?","answers":[{"answer":"magna fugiat","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit sunt","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis","points":54,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":123,"question":"Consequat velit dolor dolor nisi amet officia?","answers":[{"answer":"quis ipsum","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint","points":47,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":218,"question":"Amet esse amet esse ut et culpa adipisicing do?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"in qui","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua eiusmo","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore cupida","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi","points":78,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607561613895,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"OKEK","users":[{"ID":"POOE","name":""},{"ID":"SLOV","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"POOE","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["SLOV"],"score":358},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":33,"question":"Incididunt sit ut non?","answers":[{"answer":"est ea","points":80,"answered":true},{"answer":"fugiat culpa","points":45,"answered":true},{"answer":"culpa amet","points":56,"answered":true},{"answer":"labore eu","points":78,"answered":true},{"answer":"id","points":56,"answered":true},{"answer":"laboru exerci","points":43,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":97,"question":"Consectetur eu magna et nisi sint elit nostrud sit et occaecat?","answers":[{"answer":"eu","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"proide labori","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"ipsum est","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"est","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim cupida","points":57,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":41,"question":"Ad velit do consequat eu ea minim dolore officia ea?","answers":[{"answer":"deseru","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt labori","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida amet","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo","points":43,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":120,"question":"Ullamco enim non magna ullamco non dolor sint do?","answers":[{"answer":"fugiat","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru ex","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"anim","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec","points":56,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607561646561,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"WQQM","users":[{"ID":"BCKY","name":""}],"hostID":"BCKY","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":true,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":241,"question":"Ipsum fugiat nisi irure irure est qui voluptate ad occaecat reprehenderit?","answers":[{"answer":"elit dolore","points":33,"answered":true},{"answer":"occaec","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"except Lorem","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo elit","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex cupida","points":77,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":118,"question":"Enim aliquip anim veniam fugiat esse sint ullamco dolore reprehenderit cillum ullamco?","answers":[{"answer":"magna aliqui","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"duis","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"except et","points":60,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":10,"question":"Do id non pariatur duis duis labore eiusmod enim Lorem pariatur fugiat?","answers":[{"answer":"ullamc","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"et dolore","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor nulla","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis labori","points":35,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":33,"question":"Incididunt sit ut non?","answers":[{"answer":"est ea","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat culpa","points":45,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa amet","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"labore eu","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"laboru exerci","points":43,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607569392648,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"RHWG","users":[{"ID":"JRKB","name":""},{"ID":"SYMO","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"JRKB","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["SYMO"],"score":44},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":false,"currentStage":1,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":267,"question":"Nisi sit id exercitation anim amet laboris eiusmod excepteur culpa ipsum?","answers":[{"answer":"ad ut","points":44,"answered":true},{"answer":"amet cupida","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet mollit","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad nulla","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":61,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":65,"question":"Nisi aliquip cillum non est veniam anim Lorem dolor?","answers":[{"answer":"nisi","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore except","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam volupt","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt nulla","points":63,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":107,"question":"Esse sunt fugiat velit esse deserunt reprehenderit fugiat reprehenderit tempor commodo amet?","answers":[{"answer":"eu except","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi quis","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum cupida","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit aliqui","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida aliqui","points":48,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":196,"question":"Adipisicing ullamco proident adipisicing ullamco ad deserunt nulla?","answers":[{"answer":"ullamc","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint sunt","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit id","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":49,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607569893473,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"EXQS","users":[{"ID":"LVGF","name":""}],"hostID":"LVGF","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":71},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":118,"question":"Enim aliquip anim veniam fugiat esse sint ullamco dolore reprehenderit cillum ullamco?","answers":[{"answer":"magna aliqui","points":71,"answered":true},{"answer":"duis","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"except et","points":60,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":177,"question":"Elit incididunt qui incididunt consequat consequat amet magna dolore?","answers":[{"answer":"deseru","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor labori","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse conseq","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit commod","points":65,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":272,"question":"Est id do consectetur aliquip nostrud officia laborum quis deserunt?","answers":[{"answer":"in minim","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt nisi","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"except","points":77,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":148,"question":"Do ex cillum amet ea anim ut incididunt in?","answers":[{"answer":"duis ad","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"ipsum","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida magna","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc repreh","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"except qui","points":57,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607569917313,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"CEJV","users":[{"ID":"URZW","name":""}],"hostID":"URZW","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":369},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":2,"question":"Officia sit pariatur labore sint occaecat excepteur occaecat ad do reprehenderit?","answers":[{"answer":"magna","points":85,"answered":true},{"answer":"mollit esse","points":40,"answered":true},{"answer":"conseq","points":50,"answered":true},{"answer":"amet","points":39,"answered":true},{"answer":"minim","points":72,"answered":true},{"answer":"except occaec","points":83,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":170,"question":"Aliquip occaecat eiusmod tempor enim est tempor labore cupidatat?","answers":[{"answer":"volupt nulla","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse offici","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut consec","points":77,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":284,"question":"Lorem magna exercitation consequat?","answers":[{"answer":"laboru eu","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"et est","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh eiusmo","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt culpa","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna id","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":78,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":202,"question":"Nisi est commodo ut culpa adipisicing enim consequat aliqua tempor quis et?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit elit","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit fugiat","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori ut","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc aute","points":66,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607570008884,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"FNNE","users":[{"ID":"HBGH","name":""}],"hostID":"HBGH","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":81}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":false,"currentStage":3,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":257,"question":"Ullamco non enim aliquip eiusmod?","answers":[{"answer":"commod occaec","points":35,"answered":true},{"answer":"nisi do","points":46,"answered":true},{"answer":"deseru","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit et","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit","points":50,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":258,"question":"Commodo aliquip nisi consequat?","answers":[{"answer":"consec","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor elit","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"duis","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec","points":51,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":107,"question":"Esse sunt fugiat velit esse deserunt reprehenderit fugiat reprehenderit tempor commodo amet?","answers":[{"answer":"eu except","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi quis","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum cupida","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit aliqui","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida aliqui","points":48,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":96,"question":"Eiusmod veniam enim est do labore enim exercitation adipisicing?","answers":[{"answer":"minim cupida","points":45,"answered":false},{"answer":"qui","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa dolore","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit irure","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci conseq","points":67,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607570086778,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"BOLP","users":[{"ID":"VEXA","name":""}],"hostID":"VEXA","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":143}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":false,"currentStage":3,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":221,"question":"Laborum laborum adipisicing ex ut irure?","answers":[{"answer":"in","points":70,"answered":true},{"answer":"offici incidi","points":73,"answered":true},{"answer":"ullamc culpa","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori dolor","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa labore","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"proide","points":72,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":227,"question":"Irure culpa enim amet eu ea voluptate ullamco?","answers":[{"answer":"labore velit","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"anim ea","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam aute","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna aliqua","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut cillum","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":45,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":223,"question":"Eu eiusmod officia est id in?","answers":[{"answer":"conseq","points":45,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici irure","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq","points":60,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":92,"question":"Lorem laborum culpa sit fugiat aliquip duis occaecat voluptate occaecat?","answers":[{"answer":"adipis","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"ipsum","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori ut","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"est","points":51,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607570114189,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"ZTJF","users":[{"ID":"GJLG","name":""}],"hostID":"GJLG","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":true,"currentStage":3,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":223,"question":"Eu eiusmod officia est id in?","answers":[{"answer":"conseq","points":45,"answered":true},{"answer":"occaec","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici irure","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq","points":60,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":13,"question":"Adipisicing aliqua velit mollit excepteur velit?","answers":[{"answer":"nostru","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea duis","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla sunt","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi deseru","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"do","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt sint","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex velit","points":57,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":18,"question":"Incididunt in duis non?","answers":[{"answer":"exerci adipis","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor ad","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"do conseq","points":70,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":247,"question":"Laboris incididunt amet amet exercitation tempor fugiat ad sint reprehenderit cupidatat id?","answers":[{"answer":"est ad","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru sit","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi","points":85,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607570369107,"activeTeam":1,"started":false},{"ID":"CKXE","users":[{"ID":"ZMHA","name":""}],"hostID":"ZMHA","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":72},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":106}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":64,"question":"Qui exercitation ad consectetur irure aliqua?","answers":[{"answer":"pariat veniam","points":72,"answered":true},{"answer":"magna","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi et","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"non","points":77,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"started":false,"currentStage":3,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":196,"question":"Adipisicing ullamco proident adipisicing ullamco ad deserunt nulla?","answers":[{"answer":"ullamc","points":33,"answered":true},{"answer":"ea","points":73,"answered":true},{"answer":"eiusmo","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint sunt","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit id","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":49,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":217,"question":"Consequat est veniam eiusmod incididunt?","answers":[{"answer":"dolore","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit repreh","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit conseq","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit","points":65,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":211,"question":"Qui eu dolore ex ad duis proident laboris id culpa incididunt est?","answers":[{"answer":"ad","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt laboru","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"labore ea","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet duis","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui nisi","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna nostru","points":51,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":2,"modified":1607570453285,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"BFEI","users":[{"ID":"FEOV","name":""}],"hostID":"FEOV","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":283},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":71}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":281,"question":"Magna excepteur fugiat adipisicing incididunt?","answers":[{"answer":"exerci","points":32,"answered":true},{"answer":"repreh nisi","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida do","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"except veniam","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc magna","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"anim veniam","points":55,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":282,"question":"Excepteur aute ex ad velit minim laborum consectetur reprehenderit ullamco excepteur?","answers":[{"answer":"laboru amet","points":71,"answered":true},{"answer":"offici","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut","points":51,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":true,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":230,"question":"Culpa elit aliqua laboris nulla ex deserunt nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"ut","points":69,"answered":true},{"answer":"fugiat","points":44,"answered":true},{"answer":"mollit","points":83,"answered":true},{"answer":"qui","points":55,"answered":true}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":123,"question":"Consequat velit dolor dolor nisi amet officia?","answers":[{"answer":"quis ipsum","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint","points":47,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":4,"modified":1607570721679,"activeTeam":0,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"KECG","users":[{"ID":"HPKK","name":""}],"hostID":"HPKK","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":428},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":273,"question":"Lorem magna fugiat ad minim nulla incididunt dolore?","answers":[{"answer":"ipsum incidi","points":72,"answered":true},{"answer":"eiusmo","points":71,"answered":true},{"answer":"esse","points":73,"answered":true},{"answer":"in","points":44,"answered":true},{"answer":"dolore","points":81,"answered":true},{"answer":"esse Lorem","points":52,"answered":true},{"answer":"occaec","points":35,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":10,"question":"Do id non pariatur duis duis labore eiusmod enim Lorem pariatur fugiat?","answers":[{"answer":"ullamc","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"et dolore","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor nulla","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis labori","points":35,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":225,"question":"Pariatur irure elit minim nulla Lorem do?","answers":[{"answer":"magna","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit aliqui","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"non in","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"anim","points":33,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":16,"question":"Laborum quis consectetur enim?","answers":[{"answer":"irure tempor","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci offici","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa labori","points":43,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":4,"modified":1607570755790,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"FBXC","users":[{"ID":"HFVW","name":""}],"hostID":"HFVW","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":380},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":211,"question":"Qui eu dolore ex ad duis proident laboris id culpa incididunt est?","answers":[{"answer":"ad","points":75,"answered":true},{"answer":"volupt laboru","points":52,"answered":true},{"answer":"labore ea","points":49,"answered":true},{"answer":"amet duis","points":72,"answered":true},{"answer":"aliqui nisi","points":81,"answered":true},{"answer":"magna nostru","points":51,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":93,"question":"Id officia id ea?","answers":[{"answer":"aute proide","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim quis","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis nulla","points":76,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":127,"question":"Sint sint mollit nostrud ullamco amet incididunt tempor nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"labore","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"nostru labore","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi proide","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum occaec","points":48,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":255,"question":"Aliquip magna tempor occaecat duis id nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"dolor","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"et est","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet ad","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad","points":64,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607570838484,"activeTeam":0,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"VEYI","users":[{"ID":"DVLK","name":""}],"hostID":"DVLK","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":320},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":100,"question":"Eiusmod non ex exercitation aliqua nulla?","answers":[{"answer":"dolore","points":35,"answered":true},{"answer":"except adipis","points":59,"answered":true},{"answer":"enim offici","points":38,"answered":true},{"answer":"fugiat","points":79,"answered":true},{"answer":"incidi nostru","points":51,"answered":true},{"answer":"labori","points":58,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":26,"question":"Ex anim sunt dolore officia sunt dolor?","answers":[{"answer":"in","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis culpa","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint","points":68,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":36,"question":"Pariatur ad consequat adipisicing ipsum?","answers":[{"answer":"dolore nisi","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua ea","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse","points":79,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":229,"question":"Dolor nisi in Lorem est Lorem do ut?","answers":[{"answer":"minim dolore","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa ut","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"non qui","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut aute","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet aliqui","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam sint","points":53,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607570900450,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"DAGX","users":[{"ID":"KTAH","name":""},{"ID":"FYTG","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"KTAH","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["FYTG"],"score":654},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":379}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":194,"question":"Lorem velit non ea?","answers":[{"answer":"et","points":34,"answered":true},{"answer":"non nulla","points":68,"answered":true},{"answer":"labore","points":60,"answered":true},{"answer":"esse","points":37,"answered":true},{"answer":"occaec ex","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut ad","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt","points":40,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":41,"question":"Ad velit do consequat eu ea minim dolore officia ea?","answers":[{"answer":"deseru","points":35,"answered":true},{"answer":"volupt labori","points":73,"answered":true},{"answer":"cupida amet","points":72,"answered":true},{"answer":"eiusmo","points":43,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":2,"question":{"ID":155,"question":"Velit Lorem proident labore labore laboris eu commodo minim?","answers":[{"answer":"nisi","points":43,"answered":true},{"answer":"sit","points":58,"answered":true},{"answer":"magna aliqui","points":77,"answered":true},{"answer":"conseq esse","points":49,"answered":true},{"answer":"minim","points":76,"answered":true},{"answer":"id","points":72,"answered":true}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":true,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":252,"question":"Magna fugiat anim ipsum anim sunt sint?","answers":[{"answer":"dolor ullamc","points":85,"answered":true},{"answer":"sint esse","points":44,"answered":true},{"answer":"ullamc","points":50,"answered":true},{"answer":"repreh","points":67,"answered":true},{"answer":"ullamc","points":33,"answered":true}]}}],"currentRound":3,"modified":1607571080940,"activeTeam":0,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"OCJR","users":[{"ID":"KBIP","name":""}],"hostID":"KBIP","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":true,"currentStage":1,"answerToBeat":1,"question":{"ID":84,"question":"Cillum dolore occaecat id commodo commodo reprehenderit adipisicing?","answers":[{"answer":"conseq deseru","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis","points":35,"answered":true},{"answer":"velit","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"non irure","points":37,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":163,"question":"Laboris consectetur tempor in et duis Lorem amet deserunt enim?","answers":[{"answer":"ea sunt","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"do","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad duis","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit veniam","points":32,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":99,"question":"Amet exercitation non enim fugiat deserunt eiusmod veniam qui sunt est?","answers":[{"answer":"ad","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"except qui","points":80,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":271,"question":"Laborum culpa velit incididunt eiusmod?","answers":[{"answer":"cupida","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"non dolore","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"ipsum","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"duis labori","points":51,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607571519129,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"EHYH","users":[{"ID":"CGYD","name":""},{"ID":"IFYX","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"CGYD","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["IFYX"],"score":169},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":true,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":1,"question":{"ID":183,"question":"Consequat non incididunt sint quis quis culpa ea?","answers":[{"answer":"in deseru","points":81,"answered":true},{"answer":"nisi Lorem","points":45,"answered":true},{"answer":"cupida ipsum","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse et","points":43,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":59,"question":"Pariatur labore officia do elit nulla consectetur cillum quis dolor ut ea?","answers":[{"answer":"pariat consec","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua qui","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse ut","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui ea","points":57,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":288,"question":"Velit proident ex fugiat excepteur esse adipisicing id sunt ea?","answers":[{"answer":"occaec id","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis Lorem","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt ex","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam esse","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida aliqui","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori","points":40,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":5,"question":"Adipisicing dolor culpa dolor laboris aliqua aliquip voluptate magna ipsum?","answers":[{"answer":"conseq sit","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea elit","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"labore","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim cillum","points":67,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607575306061,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"HIHI","users":[{"ID":"BHUH","name":""}],"hostID":"BHUH","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":85},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":true,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":125,"question":"Ad voluptate amet deserunt aliquip amet dolor cillum voluptate laboris ut tempor?","answers":[{"answer":"anim irure","points":85,"answered":true},{"answer":"exerci id","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"laboru elit","points":45,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":3,"question":"Do occaecat consequat adipisicing Lorem aliqua exercitation minim nostrud fugiat non amet?","answers":[{"answer":"esse","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"et aliqui","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor ipsum","points":72,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":35,"question":"Laborum nisi proident mollit eiusmod in?","answers":[{"answer":"dolore","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor exerci","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"non enim","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua tempor","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea irure","points":69,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":12,"question":"Dolore minim dolor cupidatat do dolor nisi ipsum ut ea?","answers":[{"answer":"est anim","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"ipsum","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt pariat","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi","points":45,"answered":false},{"answer":"anim","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"in","points":76,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607575287210,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"NXLZ","users":[{"ID":"PRIF","name":""}],"hostID":"PRIF","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":165,"question":"Est sint do qui elit aute amet voluptate?","answers":[{"answer":"tempor","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis anim","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"fugiat cillum","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum repreh","points":37,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":0,"question":"Occaecat anim cillum incididunt?","answers":[{"answer":"in","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"except nulla","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua incidi","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"labore cupida","points":67,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":245,"question":"Et enim incididunt minim proident eu sunt sint magna qui?","answers":[{"answer":"ullamc volupt","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit ipsum","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"do","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu in","points":41,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":138,"question":"Mollit nisi in consequat quis elit exercitation deserunt?","answers":[{"answer":"conseq adipis","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore aliqua","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec","points":58,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607635942389,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"EJII","users":[{"ID":"KYDU","name":""}],"hostID":"KYDU","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":112},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":110}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":82,"question":"Cupidatat aute minim adipisicing aliqua aute amet sit ut aliquip?","answers":[{"answer":"elit","points":60,"answered":true},{"answer":"cillum non","points":50,"answered":true},{"answer":"culpa","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq proide","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit adipis","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis cillum","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"do","points":54,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":218,"question":"Amet esse amet esse ut et culpa adipisicing do?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit","points":33,"answered":true},{"answer":"in qui","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua eiusmo","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore cupida","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi","points":78,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":3,"started":true,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":178,"question":"Proident quis non duis?","answers":[{"answer":"cillum id","points":79,"answered":true},{"answer":"Lorem","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"laboru labori","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"pariat","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo occaec","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim nulla","points":59,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":2,"modified":1607636954640,"activeTeam":0,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"EXQW","users":[{"ID":"JENY","name":""}],"hostID":"JENY","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":82},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":80,"question":"In Lorem irure voluptate id ea?","answers":[{"answer":"minim mollit","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua incidi","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"aute","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"est Lorem","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"proide proide","points":47,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":218,"question":"Amet esse amet esse ut et culpa adipisicing do?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"in qui","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua eiusmo","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore cupida","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi","points":78,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":204,"question":"Duis voluptate elit quis in ullamco irure occaecat ex id?","answers":[{"answer":"volupt","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec nulla","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc tempor","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"proide labori","points":63,"answered":false}]}},{"number":4,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":98,"question":"Id exercitation nostrud aliqua exercitation pariatur?","answers":[{"answer":"ex","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu eu","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore labore","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec sint","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"laboru","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"in","points":85,"answered":false}]}},{"number":5,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":129,"question":"Anim est velit excepteur pariatur in qui quis est?","answers":[{"answer":"incidi et","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh tempor","points":55,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607639377834,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"HZKQ","users":[{"ID":"FBTC","name":""}],"hostID":"FBTC","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":55,"question":"Ex irure minim ipsum ut consectetur quis incididunt?","answers":[{"answer":"culpa","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"aute Lorem","points":61,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":186,"question":"Elit commodo cillum ipsum irure?","answers":[{"answer":"sit","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"ipsum","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"commod nisi","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis sit","points":43,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":59,"question":"Pariatur labore officia do elit nulla consectetur cillum quis dolor ut ea?","answers":[{"answer":"pariat consec","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua qui","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse ut","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui ea","points":57,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607639579418,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"VUYV","users":[{"ID":"DQIB","name":""}],"hostID":"DQIB","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"started":true,"currentStage":1,"answerToBeat":1,"question":{"ID":117,"question":"Nisi culpa veniam dolore duis deserunt?","answers":[{"answer":"commod","points":57,"answered":true},{"answer":"tempor occaec","points":36,"answered":true},{"answer":"aute ea","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim esse","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam nostru","points":62,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":278,"question":"Amet proident excepteur laboris deserunt?","answers":[{"answer":"incidi","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor veniam","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse aute","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui","points":75,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":266,"question":"Eu tempor incididunt aute incididunt anim ex laboris commodo?","answers":[{"answer":"cillum mollit","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici repreh","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit","points":33,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607639596409,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"ONHT","users":[{"ID":"DSBE","name":""}],"hostID":"DSBE","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":160},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":141,"question":"Reprehenderit sunt ad aute officia voluptate?","answers":[{"answer":"irure pariat","points":46,"answered":true},{"answer":"veniam","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"elit","points":45,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo enim","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru ea","points":56,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":86,"question":"Aliquip excepteur pariatur veniam officia eiusmod nisi tempor consectetur mollit dolore?","answers":[{"answer":"cupida aliqui","points":82,"answered":true},{"answer":"Lorem nisi","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore qui","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici cillum","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi aliqua","points":43,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":3,"started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":145,"question":"Anim incididunt consequat culpa culpa?","answers":[{"answer":"occaec","points":32,"answered":true},{"answer":"enim","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor","points":58,"answered":false}]}},{"number":"Rapid Rubles","type":"fast-money","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"questions":[{"ID":62,"question":"Minim aute cupidatat dolor?","answers":[{"answer":"eu","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"proide ea","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure irure","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex sit","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt","points":74,"answered":false}]},{"ID":254,"question":"Est nisi excepteur cupidatat consequat duis?","answers":[{"answer":"culpa","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"in ut","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci proide","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"in fugiat","points":32,"answered":false}]},{"ID":256,"question":"Occaecat do voluptate consequat consectetur proident magna reprehenderit?","answers":[{"answer":"ullamc","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec irure","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"et irure","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"in","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"in","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"non offici","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit ut","points":59,"answered":false}]},{"ID":185,"question":"Velit dolor ipsum consequat laboris quis ex ex?","answers":[{"answer":"eiusmo ipsum","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt labore","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit","points":42,"answered":false}]},{"ID":284,"question":"Lorem magna exercitation consequat?","answers":[{"answer":"laboru eu","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"et est","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh eiusmo","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt culpa","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna id","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":78,"answered":false}]}]}],"currentRound":3,"modified":1607722534410,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"OFIN","users":[{"ID":"NSFR","name":""}],"hostID":"NSFR","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":true,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":102,"question":"Eu magna enim laborum sint anim amet officia nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"non","points":61,"answered":true},{"answer":"id ex","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo ipsum","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis","points":84,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":283,"question":"In excepteur aliquip culpa proident ex elit nostrud in?","answers":[{"answer":"dolor ex","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi qui","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"aute","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":34,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":99,"question":"Amet exercitation non enim fugiat deserunt eiusmod veniam qui sunt est?","answers":[{"answer":"ad","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"except qui","points":80,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607722625279,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"WJYM","users":[{"ID":"VDOB","name":""}],"hostID":"VDOB","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":151},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":154,"question":"Velit minim ad esse esse in mollit tempor?","answers":[{"answer":"adipis culpa","points":62,"answered":true},{"answer":"except consec","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint repreh","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori et","points":66,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":259,"question":"Eiusmod consectetur ut consectetur et ut est?","answers":[{"answer":"dolor","points":56,"answered":true},{"answer":"eu","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci ullamc","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam laboru","points":45,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex minim","points":77,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":73,"question":"Sit minim consectetur irure aliqua?","answers":[{"answer":"qui","points":33,"answered":true},{"answer":"Lorem ipsum","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem volupt","points":38,"answered":false}]}},{"number":"Rapid Rubles","type":"fast-money","started":false,"currentStage":0,"currentQuestion":0,"answerToBeat":0,"questions":[{"ID":233,"question":"Ullamco et duis laborum mollit amet aute labore Lorem?","answers":[{"answer":"eiusmo","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa nulla","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam nostru","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"pariat","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua laboru","points":54,"answered":false}]},{"ID":229,"question":"Dolor nisi in Lorem est Lorem do ut?","answers":[{"answer":"minim dolore","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa ut","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"non qui","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut aute","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet aliqui","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam sint","points":53,"answered":false}]},{"ID":127,"question":"Sint sint mollit nostrud ullamco amet incididunt tempor nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"labore","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"nostru labore","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi proide","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum occaec","points":48,"answered":false}]},{"ID":282,"question":"Excepteur aute ex ad velit minim laborum consectetur reprehenderit ullamco excepteur?","answers":[{"answer":"laboru amet","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut","points":51,"answered":false}]},{"ID":203,"question":"Et sunt quis voluptate?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit eiusmo","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"qui ea","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"do dolor","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":38,"answered":false}]}]}],"currentRound":3,"modified":1607804870931,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"KHWW","users":[{"ID":"MRKM","name":""}],"hostID":"MRKM","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":true,"currentStage":1,"answerToBeat":1,"question":{"ID":120,"question":"Ullamco enim non magna ullamco non dolor sint do?","answers":[{"answer":"fugiat","points":60,"answered":true},{"answer":"esse","points":67,"answered":true},{"answer":"deseru ex","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"anim","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec","points":56,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":132,"question":"Qui eiusmod et est nulla enim deserunt?","answers":[{"answer":"laboru do","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori culpa","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori dolor","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea dolor","points":41,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":112,"question":"Fugiat duis ex laborum cillum anim aute exercitation labore?","answers":[{"answer":"sunt quis","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem nulla","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":57,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607806659757,"activeTeam":1,"started":false},{"ID":"PGHJ","users":[{"ID":"CEDP","name":""}],"hostID":"CEDP","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":60},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":104,"question":"Cillum aute incididunt occaecat ullamco et esse?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit do","points":60,"answered":true},{"answer":"ad mollit","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo ad","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt","points":46,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":true,"currentStage":1,"answerToBeat":2,"question":{"ID":24,"question":"Esse fugiat cupidatat nostrud magna esse ut adipisicing et aute ut id?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit volupt","points":48,"answered":true},{"answer":"laboru ullamc","points":50,"answered":true},{"answer":"cupida amet","points":55,"answered":true},{"answer":"qui exerci","points":84,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":110,"question":"Esse consequat culpa cillum aute cupidatat in et esse?","answers":[{"answer":"fugiat incidi","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"id sit","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":43,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607806686857,"activeTeam":1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"UWXH","users":[{"ID":"JXLL","name":""}],"hostID":"JXLL","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":130},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":103,"question":"Commodo est irure nostrud labore cillum veniam?","answers":[{"answer":"sunt","points":57,"answered":true},{"answer":"id","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici Lorem","points":49,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":204,"question":"Duis voluptate elit quis in ullamco irure occaecat ex id?","answers":[{"answer":"volupt","points":32,"answered":true},{"answer":"occaec nulla","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc tempor","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"proide labori","points":63,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":36,"question":"Pariatur ad consequat adipisicing ipsum?","answers":[{"answer":"dolore nisi","points":41,"answered":true},{"answer":"irure","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua ea","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse","points":79,"answered":false}]}},{"number":"Rapid Rubles","type":"fast-money","started":false,"currentStage":0,"currentQuestion":0,"answerToBeat":0,"questions":[{"ID":273,"question":"Lorem magna fugiat ad minim nulla incididunt dolore?","answers":[{"answer":"ipsum incidi","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"in","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse Lorem","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec","points":35,"answered":false}]},{"ID":49,"question":"Irure est et sit in sint aliqua sunt consectetur?","answers":[{"answer":"commod anim","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"elit","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea incidi","points":51,"answered":false}]},{"ID":192,"question":"Velit aliquip laborum id officia laboris sunt mollit est pariatur enim amet?","answers":[{"answer":"ipsum cupida","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse nulla","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu anim","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"laboru nisi","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint","points":64,"answered":false}]},{"ID":184,"question":"Eu culpa quis ex eu elit occaecat nostrud nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"tempor ut","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru non","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt enim","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor nulla","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo sunt","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci amet","points":34,"answered":false}]},{"ID":136,"question":"Ea occaecat fugiat velit aute consectetur aliqua officia voluptate excepteur?","answers":[{"answer":"eu","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq ullamc","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici occaec","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua do","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"non","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"non nulla","points":53,"answered":false}]}]}],"currentRound":3,"modified":1607806749648,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"LFUX","users":[{"ID":"BODI","name":""}],"hostID":"BODI","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":162},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":111,"question":"Irure enim laboris duis culpa amet cillum incididunt consectetur?","answers":[{"answer":"except","points":37,"answered":true},{"answer":"proide offici","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure deseru","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"commod","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"anim","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":44,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":85,"question":"Non irure consequat anim ut velit sint cupidatat?","answers":[{"answer":"Lorem","points":54,"answered":true},{"answer":"enim enim","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"non","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex sint","points":68,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":11,"question":"Consectetur irure exercitation voluptate?","answers":[{"answer":"amet adipis","points":71,"answered":true},{"answer":"offici","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici minim","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui","points":71,"answered":false}]}},{"number":"Rapid Rubles","type":"fast-money","started":false,"currentStage":0,"currentQuestion":0,"answerToBeat":0,"questions":[{"ID":166,"question":"Commodo ipsum elit enim?","answers":[{"answer":"quis","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"nostru","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"duis conseq","points":84,"answered":false}]},{"ID":118,"question":"Enim aliquip anim veniam fugiat esse sint ullamco dolore reprehenderit cillum ullamco?","answers":[{"answer":"magna aliqui","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"duis","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"except et","points":60,"answered":false}]},{"ID":50,"question":"Esse pariatur non elit est non esse?","answers":[{"answer":"fugiat aliqui","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi eiusmo","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt Lorem","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec labore","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit culpa","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec","points":56,"answered":false}]},{"ID":268,"question":"Aute mollit ea consequat velit ea proident et ex aute dolore sit?","answers":[{"answer":"amet","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"commod nulla","points":45,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"anim cupida","points":51,"answered":false}]},{"ID":295,"question":"Proident non in dolore Lorem aliquip velit qui ad amet?","answers":[{"answer":"offici","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim dolor","points":56,"answered":false}]}],"playerAnswers":[[],[]]}],"currentRound":3,"modified":1607807379031,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"PEZQ","users":[{"ID":"CBGH","name":""}],"hostID":"CBGH","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":158},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":206,"question":"Adipisicing id esse dolore ipsum dolore mollit?","answers":[{"answer":"laboru tempor","points":76,"answered":true},{"answer":"incidi","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"elit adipis","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut ad","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem do","points":69,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":36,"question":"Pariatur ad consequat adipisicing ipsum?","answers":[{"answer":"dolore nisi","points":41,"answered":true},{"answer":"irure","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua ea","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse","points":79,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":150,"question":"Non commodo labore consectetur id?","answers":[{"answer":"adipis","points":41,"answered":true},{"answer":"conseq anim","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci volupt","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":47,"answered":false}]}},{"number":"Rapid Rubles","type":"fast-money","started":true,"currentStage":0,"currentQuestion":0,"answerToBeat":0,"questions":[{"ID":135,"question":"Mollit et ad irure est pariatur esse nisi?","answers":[{"answer":"Lorem","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit aliqui","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor non","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"anim ea","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"non","points":34,"answered":false}]},{"ID":208,"question":"Anim veniam cillum voluptate amet fugiat?","answers":[{"answer":"deseru","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum elit","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim duis","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem in","points":45,"answered":false},{"answer":"et nostru","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"ipsum","points":82,"answered":false}]},{"ID":247,"question":"Laboris incididunt amet amet exercitation tempor fugiat ad sint reprehenderit cupidatat id?","answers":[{"answer":"est ad","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru sit","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi","points":85,"answered":false}]},{"ID":23,"question":"Non fugiat voluptate exercitation aute ipsum amet ex elit elit?","answers":[{"answer":"duis quis","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci exerci","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua incidi","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure id","points":59,"answered":false}]},{"ID":50,"question":"Esse pariatur non elit est non esse?","answers":[{"answer":"fugiat aliqui","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi eiusmo","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt Lorem","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec labore","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit culpa","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec","points":56,"answered":false}]}],"playerAnswers":[[],[]]}],"currentRound":3,"modified":1607817876382,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"NDIW","users":[{"ID":"LTUN","name":""}],"hostID":"LTUN","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":270,"question":"Cupidatat nostrud proident Lorem nostrud Lorem proident consectetur consequat exercitation?","answers":[{"answer":"laboru","points":63,"answered":true},{"answer":"volupt","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem cupida","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore amet","points":74,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":295,"question":"Proident non in dolore Lorem aliquip velit qui ad amet?","answers":[{"answer":"offici","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim dolor","points":56,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":54,"question":"Quis proident pariatur voluptate ipsum magna eu et fugiat esse labore?","answers":[{"answer":"quis elit","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor est","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"aute","points":46,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607819326126,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"YWCE","users":[{"ID":"FFSS","name":""}],"hostID":"FFSS","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":142},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":265,"question":"Fugiat quis nisi cillum aliquip veniam?","answers":[{"answer":"commod offici","points":39,"answered":true},{"answer":"ut","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua magna","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui aliqua","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt sint","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec except","points":45,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":241,"question":"Ipsum fugiat nisi irure irure est qui voluptate ad occaecat reprehenderit?","answers":[{"answer":"elit dolore","points":33,"answered":true},{"answer":"occaec","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"except Lorem","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo elit","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex cupida","points":77,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":72,"question":"Tempor commodo aliqua dolore officia irure sunt quis exercitation sunt velit?","answers":[{"answer":"duis in","points":70,"answered":true},{"answer":"exerci","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"non","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"commod aute","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"duis irure","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua do","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"ipsum","points":65,"answered":false}]}},{"number":"Rapid Rubles","type":"fast-money","started":false,"currentStage":0,"currentQuestion":0,"answerToBeat":0,"questions":[{"ID":118,"question":"Enim aliquip anim veniam fugiat esse sint ullamco dolore reprehenderit cillum ullamco?","answers":[{"answer":"magna aliqui","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"duis","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"except et","points":60,"answered":false}]},{"ID":9,"question":"In officia veniam commodo nulla anim eu?","answers":[{"answer":"elit id","points":75,"answered":false},{"answer":"sunt esse","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum ipsum","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"except ipsum","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori cupida","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui","points":68,"answered":false}]},{"ID":274,"question":"Sunt ex ullamco fugiat irure dolore in deserunt aliqua?","answers":[{"answer":"dolore","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici irure","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"do quis","points":80,"answered":false}]},{"ID":186,"question":"Elit commodo cillum ipsum irure?","answers":[{"answer":"sit","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"ipsum","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"commod nisi","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis sit","points":43,"answered":false}]},{"ID":108,"question":"Ad nisi commodo exercitation reprehenderit elit eiusmod incididunt reprehenderit labore eiusmod?","answers":[{"answer":"except quis","points":82,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"duis","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint sit","points":58,"answered":false}]}],"playerAnswers":[[],[]]}],"currentRound":3,"modified":1607819362302,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"YONE","users":[{"ID":"UIIH","name":""}],"hostID":"UIIH","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":122},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":23,"question":"Non fugiat voluptate exercitation aute ipsum amet ex elit elit?","answers":[{"answer":"duis quis","points":51,"answered":true},{"answer":"exerci exerci","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua incidi","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure id","points":59,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":122,"question":"Cillum culpa tempor proident eu est pariatur quis?","answers":[{"answer":"offici","points":37,"answered":true},{"answer":"et id","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit ex","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex aute","points":46,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":242,"question":"Tempor incididunt culpa ipsum dolore proident ipsum?","answers":[{"answer":"qui","points":34,"answered":true},{"answer":"Lorem","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt laboru","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"labore ut","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut","points":43,"answered":false}]}},{"number":"Rapid Rubles","type":"fast-money","started":false,"currentStage":0,"currentQuestion":0,"answerToBeat":0,"questions":[{"ID":219,"question":"Id enim reprehenderit do sunt incididunt id tempor nisi do nulla deserunt?","answers":[{"answer":"offici magna","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"qui","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"Lorem cupida","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec minim","points":76,"answered":false}]},{"ID":148,"question":"Do ex cillum amet ea anim ut incididunt in?","answers":[{"answer":"duis ad","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"ipsum","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida magna","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc repreh","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"except qui","points":57,"answered":false}]},{"ID":203,"question":"Et sunt quis voluptate?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit eiusmo","points":46,"answered":false},{"answer":"qui ea","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":40,"answered":false},{"answer":"do dolor","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":38,"answered":false}]},{"ID":248,"question":"Irure mollit voluptate voluptate aute ipsum sint quis sint pariatur esse?","answers":[{"answer":"duis","points":52,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure consec","points":36,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq aliqui","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"labore adipis","points":75,"answered":false}]},{"ID":199,"question":"Ipsum aute deserunt amet excepteur mollit?","answers":[{"answer":"magna ex","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam nostru","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"non","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis ullamc","points":39,"answered":false}]}],"playerAnswers":[[],[]]}],"currentRound":3,"modified":1607822703877,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"LYNY","users":[{"ID":"YKWH","name":""}],"hostID":"YKWH","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":45},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":96,"question":"Eiusmod veniam enim est do labore enim exercitation adipisicing?","answers":[{"answer":"minim cupida","points":45,"answered":true},{"answer":"qui","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa dolore","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit irure","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci conseq","points":67,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":5,"question":{"ID":188,"question":"Ut aute est non cupidatat duis eu?","answers":[{"answer":"fugiat","points":84,"answered":true},{"answer":"tempor","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici qui","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis dolore","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis sit","points":83,"answered":true},{"answer":"ullamc","points":82,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":175,"question":"Aliquip mollit tempor sunt esse pariatur irure?","answers":[{"answer":"fugiat quis","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint commod","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq aliqua","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore eu","points":41,"answered":false}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1607822779990,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"RIEJ","users":[{"ID":"KVMC","name":""}],"hostID":"KVMC","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":130},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":218,"question":"Amet esse amet esse ut et culpa adipisicing do?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit","points":33,"answered":true},{"answer":"in qui","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua eiusmo","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore cupida","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi","points":78,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":74,"question":"Aliqua fugiat do proident exercitation sunt duis?","answers":[{"answer":"ex dolor","points":44,"answered":true},{"answer":"aliqui offici","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi irure","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"non","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo","points":65,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":258,"question":"Commodo aliquip nisi consequat?","answers":[{"answer":"consec","points":53,"answered":true},{"answer":"volupt","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor elit","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"duis","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"occaec","points":51,"answered":false}]}},{"number":"Rapid Rubles","type":"fast-money","started":false,"currentStage":0,"currentQuestion":0,"answerToBeat":0,"questions":[{"ID":288,"question":"Velit proident ex fugiat excepteur esse adipisicing id sunt ea?","answers":[{"answer":"occaec id","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis Lorem","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt ex","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam esse","points":35,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida aliqui","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori","points":40,"answered":false}]},{"ID":156,"question":"Fugiat nisi qui officia pariatur dolore?","answers":[{"answer":"sit","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut minim","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":34,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci duis","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"incidi ex","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"consec","points":77,"answered":false}]},{"ID":94,"question":"Laboris exercitation aliquip anim pariatur deserunt pariatur incididunt cupidatat proident dolore?","answers":[{"answer":"occaec repreh","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla est","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"non","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori ad","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna dolor","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa","points":74,"answered":false}]},{"ID":82,"question":"Cupidatat aute minim adipisicing aliqua aute amet sit ut aliquip?","answers":[{"answer":"elit","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum non","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq proide","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit adipis","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis cillum","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"do","points":54,"answered":false}]},{"ID":78,"question":"Dolor do non voluptate culpa ex amet consequat aliquip sunt cupidatat mollit?","answers":[{"answer":"fugiat","points":81,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"esse ullamc","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"in laboru","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea occaec","points":71,"answered":false}]}],"playerAnswers":[[{"answer":"one","points":1,"revealed":false},{"answer":"two","points":2,"revealed":false},{"answer":"three","points":3,"revealed":false},{"answer":"four","points":4,"revealed":false},{"answer":"five","points":5,"revealed":false}],[]]}],"currentRound":3,"modified":1607823456326,"activeTeam":0,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"ZINS","users":[{"ID":"OXLQ","name":""}],"hostID":"OXLQ","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":231},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":4,"question":{"ID":65,"question":"Nisi aliquip cillum non est veniam anim Lorem dolor?","answers":[{"answer":"nisi","points":42,"answered":true},{"answer":"nulla","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore except","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam volupt","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"volupt nulla","points":63,"answered":true}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":19,"question":"Incididunt amet aliqua aute Lorem anim ea non dolore sunt qui minim?","answers":[{"answer":"conseq nostru","points":44,"answered":true},{"answer":"offici","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"nostru","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"except quis","points":80,"answered":false},{"answer":"elit velit","points":57,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":48,"question":"Consectetur laboris deserunt cillum irure nulla fugiat veniam incididunt?","answers":[{"answer":"dolore repreh","points":82,"answered":true},{"answer":"eiusmo ex","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"adipis","points":67,"answered":false}]}},{"number":"Rapid Rubles","type":"fast-money","started":false,"currentStage":1,"currentQuestion":0,"answerToBeat":0,"questions":[{"ID":205,"question":"Incididunt nisi enim enim cupidatat quis?","answers":[{"answer":"tempor","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"pariat","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":64,"answered":false},{"answer":"elit","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit","points":77,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim","points":84,"answered":false}]},{"ID":190,"question":"Consectetur commodo fugiat officia labore voluptate?","answers":[{"answer":"enim repreh","points":79,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit et","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi minim","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu dolore","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"except laboru","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa consec","points":66,"answered":false}]},{"ID":119,"question":"Quis adipisicing eiusmod proident officia proident nisi nulla deserunt duis veniam commodo?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"sit","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"nulla","points":74,"answered":false},{"answer":"in","points":69,"answered":false}]},{"ID":164,"question":"Duis minim proident minim deserunt do?","answers":[{"answer":"mollit sit","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum occaec","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"pariat","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut nulla","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"cillum ex","points":60,"answered":false}]},{"ID":259,"question":"Eiusmod consectetur ut consectetur et ut est?","answers":[{"answer":"dolor","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"exerci ullamc","points":50,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolore","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam laboru","points":45,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex minim","points":77,"answered":false}]}],"playerAnswers":[[{"answer":"one","points":1,"revealed":false},{"answer":"two","points":2,"revealed":false},{"answer":"three","points":3,"revealed":false},{"answer":"four","points":4,"revealed":false},{"answer":"five","points":5,"revealed":false}],[]]}],"currentRound":3,"modified":1607823855145,"activeTeam":0,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"WWWD","users":[{"ID":"UVXI","name":""}],"hostID":"UVXI","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":238},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":190,"question":"Consectetur commodo fugiat officia labore voluptate?","answers":[{"answer":"enim repreh","points":79,"answered":true},{"answer":"sit et","points":67,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi minim","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"eu dolore","points":43,"answered":false},{"answer":"except laboru","points":47,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa consec","points":66,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":7,"question":"Occaecat laboris cupidatat incididunt amet sit cillum nostrud?","answers":[{"answer":"tempor nulla","points":78,"answered":true},{"answer":"culpa","points":62,"answered":false},{"answer":"quis","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici","points":66,"answered":false},{"answer":"in tempor","points":72,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":126,"question":"Elit pariatur voluptate qui aliqua esse occaecat?","answers":[{"answer":"deseru","points":81,"answered":true},{"answer":"veniam quis","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"aute enim","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"aute consec","points":69,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru labori","points":49,"answered":false}]}},{"number":"Rapid Rubles","type":"fast-money","started":false,"currentStage":2,"currentQuestion":0,"answerToBeat":0,"questions":[{"ID":47,"question":"Deserunt sit incididunt dolore magna?","answers":[{"answer":"Lorem ullamc","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"except","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"veniam dolore","points":78,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex except","points":60,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqui","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":47,"answered":false}]},{"ID":95,"question":"Velit nisi ex est ad nostrud?","answers":[{"answer":"volupt aliqui","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"mollit nostru","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"magna","points":38,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"elit sit","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea","points":41,"answered":false}]},{"ID":80,"question":"In Lorem irure voluptate id ea?","answers":[{"answer":"minim mollit","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua incidi","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"aute","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"id","points":59,"answered":false},{"answer":"est Lorem","points":54,"answered":false},{"answer":"proide proide","points":47,"answered":false}]},{"ID":282,"question":"Excepteur aute ex ad velit minim laborum consectetur reprehenderit ullamco excepteur?","answers":[{"answer":"laboru amet","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"repreh","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"ut","points":51,"answered":false}]},{"ID":28,"question":"Sunt exercitation nostrud cillum?","answers":[{"answer":"aute fugiat","points":71,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure eu","points":58,"answered":false},{"answer":"pariat","points":70,"answered":false}]}],"playerAnswers":[[{"answer":"one","points":1,"revealed":false},{"answer":"two","points":2,"revealed":false},{"answer":"three","points":3,"revealed":false},{"answer":"four","points":4,"revealed":false},{"answer":"five","points":5,"revealed":false}],[{"answer":"1","points":11,"revealed":false},{"answer":"1","points":1,"revealed":false},{"answer":"1","points":1,"revealed":false},{"answer":"1","points":11,"revealed":false},{"answer":"1","points":1,"revealed":false}]]}],"currentRound":3,"modified":1607823977479,"activeTeam":0,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"OMAW","users":[{"ID":"IVUY","name":""},{"ID":"OJHV","name":"player 1"}],"hostID":"IVUY","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["OJHV"],"score":185},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":247,"question":"Laboris incididunt amet amet exercitation tempor fugiat ad sint reprehenderit cupidatat id?","answers":[{"answer":"est ad","points":74,"answered":true},{"answer":"deseru sit","points":61,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"nisi","points":85,"answered":false}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":41,"question":"Ad velit do consequat eu ea minim dolore officia ea?","answers":[{"answer":"deseru","points":35,"answered":true},{"answer":"volupt labori","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"cupida amet","points":72,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo","points":43,"answered":false}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":287,"question":"Cillum officia incididunt mollit id non dolore anim in cupidatat?","answers":[{"answer":"dolor","points":76,"answered":true},{"answer":"est conseq","points":83,"answered":false},{"answer":"dolor dolor","points":57,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":43,"answered":false}]}},{"number":"Rapid Rubles","type":"fast-money","started":false,"currentStage":2,"currentQuestion":0,"answerToBeat":0,"questions":[{"ID":221,"question":"Laborum laborum adipisicing ex ut irure?","answers":[{"answer":"in","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"offici incidi","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc culpa","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"ullamc","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"labori dolor","points":42,"answered":false},{"answer":"culpa labore","points":41,"answered":false},{"answer":"proide","points":72,"answered":false}]},{"ID":143,"question":"Do pariatur dolor elit in aliquip proident dolore occaecat occaecat aute?","answers":[{"answer":"enim ad","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"minim","points":55,"answered":false},{"answer":"duis minim","points":53,"answered":false},{"answer":"laboru","points":60,"answered":false}]},{"ID":71,"question":"Quis velit adipisicing tempor sunt veniam id veniam qui deserunt?","answers":[{"answer":"conseq","points":84,"answered":false},{"answer":"conseq incidi","points":65,"answered":false},{"answer":"ex laboru","points":76,"answered":false},{"answer":"enim","points":44,"answered":false},{"answer":"irure mollit","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"et","points":32,"answered":false},{"answer":"tempor","points":83,"answered":false}]},{"ID":198,"question":"Irure officia dolore fugiat officia?","answers":[{"answer":"aliqua","points":85,"answered":false},{"answer":"labore id","points":39,"answered":false},{"answer":"qui","points":68,"answered":false},{"answer":"deseru nulla","points":48,"answered":false},{"answer":"id deseru","points":63,"answered":false},{"answer":"aliqua elit","points":49,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad culpa","points":70,"answered":false}]},{"ID":196,"question":"Adipisicing ullamco proident adipisicing ullamco ad deserunt nulla?","answers":[{"answer":"ullamc","points":33,"answered":false},{"answer":"ea","points":73,"answered":false},{"answer":"eiusmo","points":51,"answered":false},{"answer":"ad","points":56,"answered":false},{"answer":"sint sunt","points":70,"answered":false},{"answer":"velit id","points":37,"answered":false},{"answer":"amet","points":49,"answered":false}]}],"playerAnswers":[[{"answer":"test tews","points":2,"revealed":false},{"answer":"1","points":2,"revealed":false},{"answer":"1","points":1,"revealed":false},{"answer":"1","points":1,"revealed":false},{"answer":"1","points":1,"revealed":false}],[{"answer":"oine","points":1,"revealed":false},{"answer":"two","points":2,"revealed":false},{"answer":"three","points":3,"revealed":false},{"answer":"four","points":4,"revealed":false},{"answer":"five","points":5,"revealed":false}]]}],"currentRound":3,"modified":1607829689277,"activeTeam":0,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"QLBI","users":[{"ID":"UMJI","name":""}],"hostID":"UMJI","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":2,"question":"If a witch was not paying attention to where she was flying, name something she might crash into.","answers":[{"answer":"","points":0,"answered":false,"revealed":false},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Tree","points":45},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Building","points":24},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Telephone Pole","points":7},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Power Line","points":6},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Plane","points":5},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Bird","points":4}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":4,"question":"Name a bad sport for someone who is afraid of the water.","answers":[{"answer":"","points":0,"answered":false,"revealed":false},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Swimming","points":33},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Water Polo","points":21},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Water Skiing","points":17},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Diving","points":11},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Scuba","points":6},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Surfing","points":5}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":5,"question":"Name a beverage that is served at kids birthday party.","answers":[{"answer":"","points":0,"answered":false,"revealed":false},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Kool Aid","points":36},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Punch","points":34},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Soda","points":16},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Lemonade","points":10},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Milk","points":2}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607833243719,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"SRZK","users":[{"ID":"DUVQ","name":""}],"hostID":"DUVQ","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":4,"question":"Name a bad sport for someone who is afraid of the water.","answers":[{"answer":"","points":0,"answered":false,"revealed":false},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Swimming","points":33},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Water Polo","points":21},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Water Skiing","points":17},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Diving","points":11},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Scuba","points":6},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Surfing","points":5}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":2,"question":"If a witch was not paying attention to where she was flying, name something she might crash into.","answers":[{"answer":"","points":0,"answered":false,"revealed":false},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Tree","points":45},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Building","points":24},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Telephone Pole","points":7},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Power Line","points":6},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Plane","points":5},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Bird","points":4}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":0,"question":"Name a word that most people yell at their dogs.","answers":[{"answer":"","points":0,"answered":false,"revealed":false},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"No","points":27},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Sit","points":23},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Stop","points":14},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Down","points":7},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Fetch","points":6},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Bad","points":5}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607833419069,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"STNM","users":[{"ID":"MEBF","name":""}],"hostID":"MEBF","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":3,"question":"Name a word a judge might yell out during a tennis match.","answers":[{"answer":"","points":0,"answered":false,"revealed":false},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Fault","points":25},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Foul","points":17},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Love","points":14},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Out","points":10},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Order","points":6},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Net","points":4},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Point","points":3}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":1,"question":"Name a musical instrument that is too big to carry on an airplane.","answers":[{"answer":"","points":0,"answered":false,"revealed":false},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Tuba","points":31},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Piano","points":28},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Cello","points":10},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Harp","points":9},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Drums","points":8},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Bass","points":5},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Trombone","points":4},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Saxophone","points":3}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":2,"question":"If a witch was not paying attention to where she was flying, name something she might crash into.","answers":[{"answer":"","points":0,"answered":false,"revealed":false},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Tree","points":45},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Building","points":24},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Telephone Pole","points":7},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Power Line","points":6},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Plane","points":5},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Bird","points":4}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607833463544,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"XLRU","users":[{"ID":"DVAB","name":""}],"hostID":"DVAB","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":4,"question":"Name a bad sport for someone who is afraid of the water.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Swimming","points":33},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Water Polo","points":21},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Water Skiing","points":17},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Diving","points":11},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Scuba","points":6},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Surfing","points":5}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":3,"question":"Name a word a judge might yell out during a tennis match.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Fault","points":25},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Foul","points":17},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Love","points":14},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Out","points":10},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Order","points":6},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Net","points":4},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Point","points":3}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":5,"question":"Name a beverage that is served at kids birthday party.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Kool Aid","points":36},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Punch","points":34},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Soda","points":16},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Lemonade","points":10},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Milk","points":2}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607833676439,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"TKWD","users":[{"ID":"MHLM","name":""}],"hostID":"MHLM","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":105},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":293,"question":"Name a job that requires a name tag.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Waiter","points":24},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Cashier","points":21},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Nurse","points":17},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Police Officer","points":12},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Hotel","points":7},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Flight Attendant","points":6}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":160,"question":"Name something that most American people would die for.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Country","points":36},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Freedom","points":25},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Rights","points":15},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Family","points":6}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":266,"question":"Name something that gives off light.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Lamp","points":45},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Sun","points":20},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Flashlight","points":11},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Candle","points":10},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Moon","points":5}]}},{"number":"Rapid Rubles","type":"fast-money","started":false,"currentStage":0,"currentQuestion":0,"answerToBeat":0,"questions":[{"ID":155,"question":"Name a beverage served hot.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Coffee","points":63},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Tea","points":21},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Hot Chocolate","points":12},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Apple Cider","points":2}]},{"ID":195,"question":"We asked 100 single women: Tell me something you have that has lasted longer than most of your relationships.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Shoes","points":17},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Jewelry","points":13},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"House","points":10},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Car","points":9},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Pet","points":8},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Friendships","points":8}]},{"ID":36,"question":"Name something that used to be free that there is now a charge for.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Television","points":15},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Banking","points":11},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Directory Assistance","points":5},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Parking","points":2}]},{"ID":60,"question":"Name something a little kid might do on the furniture that would tick off his parents.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Jump","points":40},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Pee","points":14},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Draw","points":13},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Spill","points":13},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Eat","points":11}]},{"ID":27,"question":"According to single men: What is the one thing you might want to know when you meet a women, but do not have the nerve to ask?","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Single","points":30},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Age","points":14},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Kids","points":7}]}],"playerAnswers":[[],[]]}],"currentRound":3,"modified":1607834309337,"activeTeam":0,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"ULRV","users":[{"ID":"KUPK","name":""}],"hostID":"KUPK","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":10,"question":"Name something a hospital uses to transport patients.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Ambulance","points":31},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Wheelchair","points":23},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Gurney","points":22},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Helicopter","points":16},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Hospital Bed","points":7}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":143,"question":"Name something that might be stolen from your car.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Stereo","points":52},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"GPS","points":12},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"CDs","points":10},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Money","points":9},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Cell Phone","points":3},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Laptop","points":2}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":14,"question":"Name something that makes you itch.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Poison Ivy","points":37},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Insect Bites","points":17},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Grass","points":5}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1607834528055,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"LYBF","users":[{"ID":"OCCP","name":""}],"hostID":"OCCP","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":100},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":2,"question":"If a witch was not paying attention to where she was flying, name something she might crash into.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Tree","points":45},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Building","points":24},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Telephone Pole","points":7},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Power Line","points":6},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Plane","points":5},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Bird","points":4}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":45,"question":"Name something a model does to make sure she looks just right for her big photo.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Fix Hair","points":23},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Makeup","points":20},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Diets","points":9},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Shaves","points":8},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Showers","points":6},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Dress","points":5}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":321,"question":"If you had a wild party, and everyone is naked, name someone you would hate to see show up.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"A Celeb","points":32},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Donald Trump","points":32},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"My Mom/Dad","points":25}]}},{"number":"Rapid Rubles","type":"fast-money","started":false,"currentStage":0,"currentQuestion":0,"answerToBeat":0,"questions":[{"ID":79,"question":"Name something people waiting for a bus might do to pass the time.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Read","points":58},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Blow Dryer","points":55},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Listen To Music","points":19},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Talk","points":13},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Text","points":10},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Curling Iron","points":10}]},{"ID":320,"question":"Some politicians belong in the White House, others belong in the _______ house?","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Jailhouse/Big House","points":36},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Dog House","points":27},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Outhouse","points":25},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Nuthouse","points":6}]},{"ID":225,"question":"Name the hardest thing to teach a dog to do.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Housebroken","points":21},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Rollover","points":15},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Fetch","points":12},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Stop Barking","points":11},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Sit","points":10},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Stay","points":8}]},{"ID":150,"question":"Name a sport women think is sexy to watch.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Baseball","points":57},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Basketball","points":57},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Football","points":14}]},{"ID":311,"question":"Name something doctors tell us to avoid.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Smoking","points":34},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Fat","points":20},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Salt","points":16},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Cholesterol","points":7},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Stress","points":4},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Red Meat","points":3}]}],"playerAnswers":[[],[]]}],"currentRound":3,"modified":1608006134422,"activeTeam":0,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"WRQF","users":[{"ID":"BUUW","name":""},{"ID":"YXQR","name":"Yakov Smirnov"},{"ID":"KZJB","name":"Yakov Smirnov"},{"ID":"EMCW","name":"gdsfsd"}],"hostID":"BUUW","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["KZJB","EMCW"],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":true,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":28,"question":"Name a holiday that people wear special colors for.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Christmas","points":51},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"St. Patrick's Day","points":28},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Fourth of July","points":12},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Easter","points":3},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Halloween","points":2}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":266,"question":"Name something that gives off light.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Lamp","points":45},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Sun","points":20},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Flashlight","points":11},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Candle","points":10},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Moon","points":5}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":263,"question":"Name the toughest part about owning an elephant as a pet.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Cleaning up after it","points":33},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Feeding him","points":31},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Too big","points":16},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"No room","points":11},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Bathing","points":9}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1608007737319,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"GEVH","users":[{"ID":"TBVC","name":""},{"ID":"KTMO","name":"gdfsafdsa"}],"hostID":"TBVC","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["KTMO"],"score":163},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":308,"question":"Name something about Santa that kids wouldn't dare to make fun of.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Big Belly","points":56},{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Beard","points":11},{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Gifts","points":10},{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Costume","points":7},{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Reindeer","points":7},{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Make Love","points":2}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":true,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":4,"question":{"ID":274,"question":"Name a reason a kiss might be bad.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Cheating","points":31},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Germs","points":26},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Bad Breath","points":19},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Unwanted","points":10},{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Too Wet","points":4}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":195,"question":"We asked 100 single women: Tell me something you have that has lasted longer than most of your relationships.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Shoes","points":17},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Jewelry","points":13},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"House","points":10},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Car","points":9},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Pet","points":8},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Friendships","points":8}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1608007846081,"activeTeam":0,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"UWVS","users":[{"ID":"KPKL","name":""}],"hostID":"KPKL","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":112},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":223,"question":"Name something someone does to keep from laughing.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Bite Your Lips","points":28},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Hold Breath","points":13},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Cover Mouth","points":11},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Clench Your Teeth","points":7},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Cough","points":5},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Think Something Sad","points":4}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":true,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":287,"question":"What's the favorite food of most people in this country.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Pizza","points":42},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Hamburger","points":21},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"French Fries","points":17},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Steak","points":6},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Ice Cream","points":4}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":246,"question":"Name a type of ring that people wear.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Wedding","points":58},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Diamond","points":12},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Engagement","points":11},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Earring","points":5},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Class ring","points":3}]}}],"currentRound":1,"modified":1608007883423,"activeTeam":0,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"TUNU","users":[{"ID":"OEFY","name":""}],"hostID":"OEFY","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":true,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":302,"question":"What is your favorite part of a wedding?","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Reception","points":50},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"End","points":19},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Ceremony","points":13},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Kiss","points":11},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Bride","points":4}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":151,"question":"Which actor's specialty is playing \"nut cases?\"","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Jim Carrey","points":19},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Robin Williams","points":16},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Steve Martin","points":6}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":0,"question":"Name a word that most people yell at their dogs.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"No","points":27},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Sit","points":23},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Stop","points":14},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Down","points":7},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Fetch","points":6},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Bad","points":5}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1608007898273,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"FXSM","users":[{"ID":"CIEJ","name":""}],"hostID":"CIEJ","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":242},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":135,"question":"Name something you might put on your armpits if you ran out of deodorant.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Perfume","points":37},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Baby Powder","points":25},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Baking Soda","points":15},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Soap","points":12},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Lotion","points":3},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Lemon","points":2}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":297,"question":"Name something most people open at least once a day.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Door","points":32},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Refrigerator","points":27},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Mail","points":25},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Mouth","points":6},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Eyes","points":3}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":3,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":4,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":318,"question":"Name a Disney villain people might dress up as for Halloween.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Cruella De Vil","points":47},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Captain Hook","points":24},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Maleficent","points":18},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Jafar","points":11}]}},{"number":"Rapid Rubles","type":"fast-money","started":false,"currentStage":0,"currentQuestion":0,"answerToBeat":0,"questions":[{"ID":130,"question":"Name a cartoon character you can have your picture taken with at Disneyland.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Mickey Mouse","points":57},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Goofy","points":14},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Minnie Mouse","points":5}]},{"ID":227,"question":"Name someplace people go that begins with the letter \"M\".","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Movies","points":26},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Mall","points":13},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Miami","points":11},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Mexico","points":8},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Museum","points":7}]},{"ID":22,"question":"Tell me a bad job for someone who hates horses.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Jockey","points":44},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Stable Hand","points":13},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Horse Trainer","points":12},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Farmer","points":9},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Rancher","points":6},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Veterinarian","points":6}]},{"ID":110,"question":"Tell me a word you might use to describe Bill Gates.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Rich","points":61},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Intelligent","points":10},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Ugly","points":6},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Microsoft","points":4},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Liberal","points":3}]},{"ID":295,"question":"Name something people do more of on vacation.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Eat Out","points":26},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Relax","points":22},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Spend Money","points":13},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Travel","points":8},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Have Fun","points":7},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"See Sights","points":6}]}],"playerAnswers":[[],[]]}],"currentRound":3,"modified":1608009613132,"activeTeam":0,"started":false,"currentStage":4},{"ID":"SDRU","users":[{"ID":"KQSD","name":""}],"hostID":"KQSD","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":true,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":119,"question":"Name something that might be half-black and half-white.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Animal","points":37},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Cookie","points":20},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Person","points":10},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Newspaper","points":9},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Ying Yang Symbol","points":7}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":86,"question":"Name a color the sky turns when the weather gets bad.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Gray","points":54},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Black","points":23},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Green","points":6},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Dark Blue","points":5},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Red","points":4}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":73,"question":"Name an animal you hope you could outrun if it were chasing you.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Bear","points":40},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Tiger","points":5},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Cheetah","points":4}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1608009791732,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"YCTM","users":[{"ID":"FFFL","name":""},{"ID":"KBIY","name":"gfds"}],"hostID":"FFFL","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":["KBIY"],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":true,"currentStage":2,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":193,"question":"Name another word for motion picture.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Movie","points":56},{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Film","points":18},{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Flick","points":6},{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Talkie","points":5},{"revealed":false,"answered":true,"answer":"Feature","points":5},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Cinema","points":4}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":36,"question":"Name something that used to be free that there is now a charge for.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Television","points":15},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Banking","points":11},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Directory Assistance","points":5},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Parking","points":2}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":48,"question":"Name a wild animal you would find living in cities.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Rats","points":24},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Raccoon","points":21},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Deer","points":5},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Skunks","points":3}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1608009935008,"activeTeam":0,"started":false},{"ID":"ODLM","users":[{"ID":"XJLS","name":""}],"hostID":"XJLS","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[],"currentRound":0,"modified":1608009850283,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false},{"ID":"BOWM","users":[{"ID":"QFYG","name":""}],"hostID":"QFYG","teams":[{"name":"Team 1","players":[],"score":0},{"name":"Team 2","players":[],"score":0}],"rounds":[{"number":1,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":8,"question":"Besides snow, name something you would need to make a snowman.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Carrot","points":21},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Coal","points":19},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Hat","points":13}]}},{"number":2,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":34,"question":"Name something your parents still give you.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Love","points":30},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Money","points":27},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Advice","points":12},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Gifts","points":8},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Grief","points":7},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Clothes","points":5},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Food","points":2}]}},{"number":3,"strikes":0,"type":"regular","started":false,"currentStage":0,"answerToBeat":0,"question":{"ID":313,"question":"Name a children's story with a wolf in it.","answers":[{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Red Ridinghood","points":60},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Three Little Pigs","points":25},{"revealed":false,"answered":false,"answer":"Peter and the Wolf","points":7}]}}],"currentRound":0,"modified":1608009906369,"activeTeam":-1,"started":false}]